<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Solve Info</title>
  
  <subtitle>Enjoy life easier but more creative!</subtitle>
  <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/"/>
  <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.260Z</updated>
  <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Ronald</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Optimized with the Help of Cookiebot Technology</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/optimized-with-the-help-of-cookiebot-technology/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/optimized-with-the-help-of-cookiebot-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.260Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.260Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Optimized-with-the-Help-of-Cookiebot-Technology"><a href="#Optimized-with-the-Help-of-Cookiebot-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Optimized with the Help of Cookiebot Technology"></a>Optimized with the Help of Cookiebot Technology</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Blue-Prism-Automates-SBA-PPP-Loan-Processing-at-Banks-Saving-More-Than-85-000-Jobs-and-Helping-Small-Businesses-Stay-Afloat"><a href="#Blue-Prism-Automates-SBA-PPP-Loan-Processing-at-Banks-Saving-More-Than-85-000-Jobs-and-Helping-Small-Businesses-Stay-Afloat" class="headerlink" title="Blue Prism Automates SBA PPP Loan Processing at Banks Saving More Than 85,000 Jobs and Helping Small Businesses Stay Afloat"></a>Blue Prism Automates SBA PPP Loan Processing at Banks Saving More Than 85,000 Jobs and Helping Small Businesses Stay Afloat</h2><p>June 10, 2020</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><h4 id="Proven-Solution-Supports-Rounds-of-Federal-Funding-Enabling-Same-Day-Processing-of-Thousands-of-Applications-from-Submissions-Bank-Review-Underwriting-SBA-Reporting-Approvals-and-Payment"><a href="#Proven-Solution-Supports-Rounds-of-Federal-Funding-Enabling-Same-Day-Processing-of-Thousands-of-Applications-from-Submissions-Bank-Review-Underwriting-SBA-Reporting-Approvals-and-Payment" class="headerlink" title="Proven Solution Supports Rounds of Federal Funding, Enabling Same-Day Processing of Thousands of Applications from Submissions, Bank Review, Underwriting, SBA Reporting, Approvals and Payment"></a><em>Proven Solution Supports Rounds of Federal Funding, Enabling Same-Day Processing of Thousands of Applications from Submissions, Bank Review, Underwriting, SBA Reporting, Approvals and Payment</em></h4><p><a class="link"   href="http://www.blueprism.com/" >Blue Prism <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> has teamed-up with <a class="link"   href="https://www.lateetud.com/" >Lateetud <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to support the US government’s latest COVID-19 relief efforts for small businesses, by helping to automate loan applications during the two rounds of funding, $349 billion and $310 billion respectively, allocated by Congress as part of its <a class="link"   href="https://www.sba.gov/" >SBA Paycheck Protection Program (PPP) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. The solution, currently being used by several U.S. banks, uses Digital Workers to automate process loan applications in a matter of seconds, for same-day approvals.</p><p>The PPP is designed to serve as a lifeline for small businesses with fewer than 500 employees until the economy reopens. By effectively automating the loan approval process, this partnership will be essential in the rapid processing of these loans and helping small businesses stay afloat. With the second round of PPP funding drying up, thousands of potential borrowers that are looking for aid during the pandemic may be shut out.</p><p>The daily demand for loans is more than the SBA processes in an entire year. Loan applicants are frustrated with the amount of time it takes to process the loan applications end-to-end, including filing and receiving timely status updates. To keep up, First Home Bank partnered with Blue Prism, Lateetud and ABBYY to automate the entire end-to-end loan application and submission process.</p><p>Below is a breakdown of the benefits the bank has received automating its SBA PPP loan approval process.</p><ul><li>10 digital workers have the capacity to process up to 14,000 loan applications per-day</li><li>30x faster than completing the process manually</li><li>Entire automated end-to-end process in under two minutes</li><li>Production ready in less than two days</li><li>Due diligence and fraud detection checking</li><li>Enterprise security and scalability</li><li>Full audit trail, 100 percent compliance and accuracy</li><li>Deploy on-prem or cloud platform of choice (Azure, AWS, Google)</li></ul><p>“The ability to respond and automate at this hyper-level is a game changer and made a real difference in people’s lives,” <strong>says Thomas Zernick, President, SBA Lending Division of at First Home Bank</strong>. “We are closing in on saving around 85,000 jobs and $770 mil in loans secured. With Lateetud delivering Blue Prism’s Digital Workforce, 99 percent of loans are processed on the day of application. We are also using the technology to automate upstream and downstream activities like application validation and loan closures, respectively. As a next step we are working with Lateetud and Blue Prism on automating the loan forgiveness process.”</p><p>While SBA’s mandate prohibits the use of RPA GUI interfaces into E-Tran, Blue Prism and Lateetud have a solution available immediately with XML file upload access into E-Tran, which adheres to the [latest SBA policy](<a class="link"   href="https://www.sba.gov/sites/default/files/2020-04/SBA%20XML" >https://www.sba.gov/sites/default/files/2020-04/SBA%20XML <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> Submission Guidance Memo 4-26-20.pdf). The value proposition of accelerating the end-to-end process from application submission, to bank review and approval, underwriting, SBA upload and payment remains strong. In addition, Blue Prism has extended the capability to other emerging applications including SBA PPP loan forgiveness, good standing checks, void checks for fraud, OFAC checks, and mortgage forbearance. To learn more about the Blue Prism, ABBYY and Lateetud solution click <a class="link"   href="https://www.blueprism.com/rpa-paycheck-protection-program/" >here <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>“We saw this challenge and it had all the right attributes for the type of Intelligent Automation (IA) solutions we create using Blue Prism, ABBYY and other AI technologies to help our banking customers. It was beset with large volume, short time span and manual steps,” <strong>says Pawan Jadhav, CEO of Lateetud, an Intelligent Process Automation company.</strong> “As part of the next phase in SBA PPP, we’ve created loan forgiveness solution powered by Blue prism and other AI technologies to help banks tackle this complex and laborious process and like the previous solution it can be deployed in matter of days.”</p><p>“This is a time when organizations need AI enabling tools to quickly ramp up their automation efforts and enhance business process efficiency,” <strong>says Neil Murphy, Vice President of Global Business Development at ABBYY, a Digital Intelligence company.</strong> “The complexity of processing various forms of documents for SBA PPP loan forgiveness is simplified with content intelligence solutions that quickly and accurately digitize, understand and process data provided by small businesses. Our goal is to take the content-centric process burdens from financial services organizations so they can focus on serving their customers.”</p><p><strong>About Blue Prism</strong></p><p>Blue Prism’s vision is to provide a Digital Workforce for Every Enterprise. The company’s purpose is to unleash the collaborative potential of humans, operating in harmony with a Digital Workforce, so every enterprise can exceed their business goals and drive meaningful growth, with unmatched speed and agility.</p><p><em>Fortune 500</em> and public-sector organizations, among customers across 70 commercial sectors, trust Blue Prism’s enterprise-grade connected-RPA platform, which has users in more than 170 countries. By strategically applying intelligent automation, these organizations are creating new opportunities and services, while unlocking massive efficiencies that return millions of hours of work back into their business.</p><p>Available on-premises, in the cloud, hybrid, or as an integrated SaaS solution, Blue Prism’s Digital Workforce automates ever more complex, end-to-end processes that drive a true digital transformation, collaboratively, at scale and across the entire enterprise.</p><p>Visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.blueprism.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> to learn more or follow Blue Prism on Twitter @blue_prism and on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/blue-prism-limited/" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><strong>Media Contacts</strong></p><p>Andre Fuochi</p><p>Blue Prism</p><p>Mobile: +1 469-394-7274</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >andre.fuochi@blueprism.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4737285&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/b2f83c409ce63012229fb9cd465bdcfe/products/copy_reporting_system.png"                      border="0"                >  KoolReport Pro  is an advanced solution for creating data reports and dashboards in PHP. Equipped with all  extended packages , KoolReport Pro is able to connect to various datasources, perform advanced data analysis, construct stunning charts and graphs and export your beautiful work to PDF, Excel, JPG or other formats. Plus, it includes powerful built-in reports such as pivot report and drill-down report which will save your time in building ones. </p><p> It will help you to write dynamic data reports easily, to construct intuitive dashboards or to build a whole business intelligence cockpit. </p><p>  KoolReport Pro  package goes with Full Source Code, Royal Free, ONE (1) Year Priority Support, ONE (1) Year Free Upgrade and 30-Days Money Back Guarantee. </p><p>  Developer License  allows  Single Developer  to create Unlimited Reports, deploy on Unlimited Servers and able deliver the work to Unlimited Clients. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Optimized-with-the-Help-of-Cookiebot-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Optimized-with-the-Help-of-Cookiebot-Technology&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Natasha Mann - Leading Visionary on the ABBYY Board</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/natasha-mann-leading-visionary-on-the-abbyy-board/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/natasha-mann-leading-visionary-on-the-abbyy-board/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.252Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.252Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Natasha-Mann-Leading-Visionary-on-the-ABBYY-Board"><a href="#Natasha-Mann-Leading-Visionary-on-the-ABBYY-Board" class="headerlink" title="Natasha Mann - Leading Visionary on the ABBYY Board"></a>Natasha Mann - Leading Visionary on the ABBYY Board</h2><h2 id="Natasha-Mann"><a href="#Natasha-Mann" class="headerlink" title="Natasha Mann"></a>Natasha Mann</h2><p>Board of Director</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/company/management/headshots/cards-headshots/743x418_natasha_mann.jpg?h=418&iar=0&w=743"                      alt="743x418_Natasha_Mann"                ></p><h4 id="Natasha-Mann-serves-as-a-Board-of-Director-at-ABBYY-where-she-works-with-the-CEO-and-executive-management-team-to-accelerate-ABBYY’s-market-leadership-as-an-intelligent-automation-solutions-provider-and-drive-the-company’s-growth-strategy-globally"><a href="#Natasha-Mann-serves-as-a-Board-of-Director-at-ABBYY-where-she-works-with-the-CEO-and-executive-management-team-to-accelerate-ABBYY’s-market-leadership-as-an-intelligent-automation-solutions-provider-and-drive-the-company’s-growth-strategy-globally" class="headerlink" title="Natasha Mann serves as a Board of Director at ABBYY where she works with the CEO and executive management team to accelerate ABBYY’s market leadership as an intelligent automation solutions provider and drive the company’s growth strategy globally."></a>Natasha Mann serves as a Board of Director at ABBYY where she works with the CEO and executive management team to accelerate ABBYY’s market leadership as an intelligent automation solutions provider and drive the company’s growth strategy globally.</h4><p>Natasha is a Principal at Marlin Equity Partners where her primary responsibilities include deal qualification, conducting due diligence, transaction execution and support and portfolio monitoring. Prior to joining Marlin, she worked at TSG Consumer Partners and TPG Growth where she specialized in leveraged buyouts and growth equity investments across the consumer, technology and telecom sectors. Previously, Natasha worked at Deutsche Bank in the Technology, Media &amp; Telecom Group where she focused on mergers and acquisitions, debt and equity financings, and other strategic advisory initiatives. Natasha earned a B.S. in Business Administration with concentration in Finance, Accounting, and Business Economics and Public Policy from the Kelley School of Business at Indiana University.</p><h3 id="Ready-to-speak-with-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-speak-with-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to speak with an expert?"></a>Ready to speak with an expert?</h3><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Schedule a demo <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Get in touch <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713321&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVDJ1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV DJ Pro</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Natasha-Mann-Leading-Visionary-on-the-ABBYY-Board&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Natasha-Mann-Leading-Visionary-on-the-ABBYY-Board&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; t</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Leveraging Cookiebot Solutions: Boosting Online Traffic &amp; Conversion Rates</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/leveraging-cookiebot-solutions-boosting-online-traffic-and-conversion-rates/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/leveraging-cookiebot-solutions-boosting-online-traffic-and-conversion-rates/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.248Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.248Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Leveraging-Cookiebot-Solutions-Boosting-Online-Traffic-Conversion-Rates"><a href="#Leveraging-Cookiebot-Solutions-Boosting-Online-Traffic-Conversion-Rates" class="headerlink" title="Leveraging Cookiebot Solutions: Boosting Online Traffic &amp; Conversion Rates"></a>Leveraging Cookiebot Solutions: Boosting Online Traffic &amp; Conversion Rates</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Zurück zu ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Ein-Leitfaden-fur-die-Verarbeitung-elektronischer-Rechnungen-in-der-Kreditorenbuchhaltung"><a href="#Ein-Leitfaden-fur-die-Verarbeitung-elektronischer-Rechnungen-in-der-Kreditorenbuchhaltung" class="headerlink" title="Ein Leitfaden für die Verarbeitung elektronischer Rechnungen in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung"></a>Ein Leitfaden für die Verarbeitung elektronischer Rechnungen in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung</h2><h6 id="Slavena-Hristova"><a href="#Slavena-Hristova" class="headerlink" title="Slavena Hristova"></a>Slavena Hristova</h6><p>6. Mai 2024</p><p>In den letzten Jahren hat die Einführung der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung (E-Invoicing) die Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung vorangetrieben und so die Abwicklung von Rechnungsvorgängen in Unternehmen verändert. </p><p>Gehe direkt zu:</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Was ist die elektronische Rechnungsstellung? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Wie funktioniert die elektronische Rechnungsstellung? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Was sind die Vorteile der e-Rechnung? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Erwartungen im Vergleich zur Realität: e-Rechnungen in dem Rechnungsverarbeitungsprozess <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Wie Sie die e-Rechnung in der automatisierten Rechnungsverarbeitung integrieren <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Die Wahl der richtigen Lösung zur Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung für Ihre elektronische Rechnungsstellung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Die elektronische Rechnungsstellung ist nicht gerade eine neue Idee, konnte sich aber bedingt durch technologische Fortschritte und verschiedene Regulierungsmaßnahmen, insbesondere in der Europäischen Union (EU), in jüngster Zeit zunehmend etablieren. Diese Maßnahmen zielen darauf ab, die Mehrwertsteuerlücke zu verringern und die finanzielle Transparenz zu erhöhen. </p><p>Im Zuge der Anpassung des Geschäftsumfelds ist es für Unternehmen entscheidend, sowohl die Hürden als auch die Vorteile der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung und -verarbeitung zu erkennen. Zu den Herausforderungen gehören der Umgang mit unterschiedlichen internationalen Standards, die Einhaltung von Vorschriften und die reibungslose Integration in bestehende Systeme. Dennoch kann die elektronische Rechnungsstellung, wenn sie mit einer durchdachten Strategie und der richtigen Technologie umgesetzt wird, die Effizienz, Genauigkeit und Umweltfreundlichkeit einer automatisiertenRechnungsverarbeitung in verschiedenen Sektoren erheblich verbessern.</p><h2 id="Was-ist-die-elektronische-Rechnungsstellung"><a href="#Was-ist-die-elektronische-Rechnungsstellung" class="headerlink" title="Was ist die elektronische Rechnungsstellung?"></a>Was ist die elektronische Rechnungsstellung?</h2><p>Elektronische Rechnungsstellung (E-Invoicing) ist der digitale Austausch von Rechnungen, die einem strukturierten, maschinenlesbaren Datenformat (wie JSON oder XML) folgen und automatisch in das ERP-System des Käufers importiert werden können, ohne dass eine manuelle Eingabe der Daten erforderlich ist. </p><p>Definitionsgemäß ist das Hauptziel einer elektronischen Rechnung der automatische Import in das Rechnungsverarbeitungssystem. Eine visuelle Darstellung der Daten in einem für den Menschen lesbaren Format (z. B. PDF) ist zwar möglich, aber zweitrangig, nicht zwingend notwendig und nicht als Teil der Rechnung angesehen. </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.movavi.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=MOVAVI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.movavi.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DMovavi%2BScreen%2BRecorder%2Bbox"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://mcusercontent.com/0885a03ded3d480dca9287f12/images/f026b149-fc7c-fd54-5f3e-1460bbb19b6b.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Wie-funktioniert-die-elektronische-Rechnungsstellung"><a href="#Wie-funktioniert-die-elektronische-Rechnungsstellung" class="headerlink" title="Wie funktioniert die elektronische Rechnungsstellung?"></a>Wie funktioniert die elektronische Rechnungsstellung?</h2><p>Die elektronische Rechnungsstellung automatisiert den gesamten Rechnungsprozess, von der Rechnungserstellung und Datenübertragung bis hin zur Validierung und Integration in die Systeme des Kunden, was zu einem effizienteren, genaueren und optimierten Arbeitsablauf in der Rechnungsverarbeitung führt. </p><p>Technisch gesehen sind elektronische Rechnungen kein neues Konzept. Neben Technologiestandards wie EDIFACT, UBL 2.0 oder eFF (Electronic Flexible Format), die in den letzten 20 Jahren für den elektronischen Datenaustausch in verschiedenen Szenarien verwendet wurden, gibt es verschiedene spezifische Formate für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung, wie z. B. </p><ul><li>ZUGFeRD&#x2F;Factur-X in Deutschland und Frankreich,</li><li>FatturaPA in Italien,</li><li>Svefaktura in Schweden</li><li>und viele weitere*. Diese entstanden vor allem, weil Privatunternehmen in Branchen mit hohem Auftragsvolumen effiziente Rechnungsverarbeitungsprozesse benötigten.</li></ul><h2 id="Was-sind-die-Vorteile-der-e-Rechnung"><a href="#Was-sind-die-Vorteile-der-e-Rechnung" class="headerlink" title="Was sind die Vorteile der e- Rechnung?"></a>Was sind die Vorteile der e- Rechnung?</h2><p>Die elektronische Rechnungsstellung bietet Unternehmen Vorteile wie Effizienz, Datengenauigkeit, Transparenz, Sicherheit und die Möglichkeit zur Kostensenkung. </p><p>Ausschlaggebend sind jedoch die Schließung der „<a class="link"   href="https://www.allenovery.com/en-gb/global/news-and-insights/publications/closing-the-gap-the-2023-eu-vat-gap-report-and-beyond" >Mehrwertsteuerlücke <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>“ und die Sicherstellung der Finanzierung des öffentlichen Sektors und nicht nur die Verbesserung der Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung sowie der Effizienz von Unternehmen. <a class="link"   href="https://taxation-customs.ec.europa.eu/taxation/value-added-tax-vat/fight-against-vat-fraud/vat-gap%5Fde" >Der „Bericht zur Mehrwertsteuerlücke 2023“ der EU-Kommission <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> ergab eine Lücke von 61 Milliarden Euro aufgrund von Betrug, Hinterziehung und Fehlberechnungen. Länder wie Italien und Polen, die eine elektronische Rechnungsstellung vorschreiben, haben ihre Mehrwertsteuerlücken erheblich verringert. </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/jssmedia/Project/Abbyy/Abbyy/Insights/Blog/A%20Guide%20to%20E-invoicing%20in%20Accounts%20Payable/guide-to-e-invoicing-accounts-payable-a-848x44.jpg"                      alt="guide-to-e-invoicing-accounts-payable-a-848x44"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.systoolsgroup.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=SYSTOOBY&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.systoolsgroup.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DSysTools%2BGmail%2BBackup"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.systoolsgroup.com/box/gmail-backup.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>Der Vorschlag zur <a class="link"   href="https://www.ey.com/en%5Fgr/tax/tax-alerts/eu-proposals-for-vat-in-the-digital-age-vida" >Mehrwertsteuer im digitalen Zeitalter (VAT in the Digital Age – ViDA) von 2022 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> zielt darauf ab, eine grenzüberschreitende digitale Berichterstattung mit elektronischer Rechnungsstellung für B2B-Transaktionen einzuführen, während <a class="link"   href="https://peppol.org/about/for-end-users/" >PEPPOL <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>-Rechnungen für B2G-Transaktionen obligatorisch werden. Viele EU-Staaten planen, die elektronische Rechnungsstellung bei B2B-Transaktionen innerhalb von vier Jahren durchzusetzen, was einen zunehmenden Trend zur gesetzlichen Einführung von Standards für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung widerspiegelt. </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://modlily.sjv.io/c/5597632/2072819/17059" target="_top" id="2072819"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17059-2072819"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2072819/17059"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Welche-Auswirkungen-hat-die-elektronische-Rechnungsstellung-auf-Rechnungsverarbeitungsprozesse"><a href="#Welche-Auswirkungen-hat-die-elektronische-Rechnungsstellung-auf-Rechnungsverarbeitungsprozesse" class="headerlink" title="Welche Auswirkungen hat die elektronische Rechnungsstellung auf Rechnungsverarbeitungsprozesse?"></a>Welche Auswirkungen hat die elektronische Rechnungsstellung auf Rechnungsverarbeitungsprozesse?</h2><p>Die Vorteile der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung für die Staatskasse sind unbestreitbar, und die ersten Ergebnisse sind bereits beeindruckend. Aus Unternehmenssicht bietet die Umstellung vom Scannen und manuellen Verarbeiten von Papier- und PDF-Rechnungen auf standardisierte elektronische Formate ebenfalls erhebliche Effizienzvorteile. </p><p>Zumindest in der Theorie verspricht das Konzept, viele Effizienzprobleme zu lösen. In der Praxis stehen die Unternehmen jedoch weiterhin vor Herausforderungen, die sich zwar von denen der Papierrechnungen unterscheiden, aber dennoch eine Lösung erfordern. Betrachten wir also vier Herausforderungen bei der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung aus der Perspektive der Erwartungen im Vergleich zur Realität. </p><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Erwartung an die elektronische Rechnungsstellung</strong></th><th><strong>Realität der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung</strong></th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td><strong>Standardisiertes Format</strong>  Strukturierte Rechnungsdaten werden digital und vollautomatisch zwischen Verkäufer und Käufer ausgetauscht. Kein manuelles Eingreifen erforderlich.</td><td><strong>Hybride Rechnungsstellung für internationale Geschäfte</strong>  Unternehmen, die grenzüberschreitend und weltweit tätig sind, müssen sich einerseits mit einer Vielzahl verschiedener nationaler Standards für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung auseinandersetzen, andererseits mit unterschiedlichen Vorschriften für Lieferanten verschiedener Größen und mit unterschiedlichen Reifegraden der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung in den einzelnen Ländern. Dies hat zur Folge, dass die Unternehmen ganz unterschiedliche Rechnungsformate handhaben müssen, die auf Papier, als PDF und in elektronischer Form eingehen und vereinheitlicht werden müssen, um dann in ein und dasselbe ERP-System zu fließen. <strong>Unterschiedliche Standards im internationalen Geschäft</strong>  Im Laufe der letzten 20 Jahre haben viele Länder weltweit ihre nationalen Standards für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung entwickelt. Reifegrad und Verbreitung solcher Standards sind ganz unterschiedlich, wobei einige Vorreiter wie Italien, die skandinavischen Länder und Lateinamerika fast 100 % aller Rechnungen elektronisch ausstellen, während Asien und Afrika noch in der Anfangsphase sind. Unternehmen, die international tätig sind, müssen sich daher mit einer Vielzahl von Standards, Konzepten und Regeln beschäftigen.  Das Netzwerk PEPPOL (Pan-European Public Procurement OnLine) verspricht, ein Schritt in die richtige Richtung zu sein und mit der Zeit solche nationalen Standards vollständig zu ersetzen. Das Netzwerk wird teilweise auch von außereuropäischen Ländern wie den USA, Mexiko, Japan, Australien und Singapur genutzt. <strong>Abweichende Auslegung des Standards</strong> Die Festlegung eines technischen Formats bedeutet nicht zwangsläufig, dass der Standard für alle Rechnungen in der gleichen Weise verwendet wird. Unterschiedliche Auslegungen des Standards durch verschiedene Lieferanten führen dazu, dass auf der Käuferseite eine Vereinheitlichung erforderlich ist, um eine reibungslose Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung zu erreichen.</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Einhaltung gesetzlicher Bestimmungen</strong>  Die Anwendung eines Standards für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung gewährleistet die Einhaltung der Vorschriften und gibt sowohl den Lieferanten als auch den Käufern Sicherheit.</td><td><strong>Ständig weiterentwickelnde Vorschriften</strong> Obwohl die Absicht klar ist, dass alle Beteiligten (zumindest in der EU) denselben Standard folgen und die grenzüberschreitende Einhaltung gewährleisten sollen, bleibt die Realität bestehen, dass sich die Gesetze und Vorschriften der Mitgliedsstaaten immer noch in ihrem eigenen Tempo weiterentwickeln und oft unklar ist, in welche Richtung.</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nahtlose Datenübertragung zwischen Systemen</strong> Ein internationaler Standard für den elektronischen Austausch von Rechnungsdaten beseitigt alle Ineffizienzen und Hindernisse auf dem Weg zur Digitalisierung. Daten werden automatisch und ohne menschliches Eingreifen zwischen Organisationen übertragen.</td><td><strong>Integration von Plattformen für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung</strong>  Die Integration verschiedener elektronischer Rechnungsstellungssysteme, die unterschiedliche Protokolle unterstützen, in bestehende, manchmal dezentralisierte ERP- und Buchhaltungssysteme kann schwierig und zeitaufwendig sein und zu Datenverlusten oder Problemen mit der Einhaltung von Vorschriften führen. <strong>Änderungsmanagement und Einführung neuer interner Verfahren</strong>  Nach Angaben von Billentis, einem Beratungsunternehmen für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung, betrachten 40 % der größeren Unternehmen dies als Hindernis für die Einführung der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung.</td></tr><tr><td><strong>100 % genaue Daten und berührungslose Rechnungsverarbeitung</strong>  Mit einem Verfahren, das die manuelle Dateneingabe oder sogar das Scannen und OCR überflüssig macht, weil alle erforderlichen Daten in einem strukturierten, maschinenlesbaren Format übermittelt werden, entfällt die Notwendigkeit einer manuellen Überprüfung und Validierung. Die Daten können direkt in das ERP-System fließen und automatisch verarbeitet werden.</td><td><strong>Validierung der Daten</strong>  Elektronische Rechnungsstellungssysteme bieten zwar Mechanismen zur Validierung von Steuerberechnungen und prüfen die Einhaltung gesetzlicher Vorschriften, doch müssen die Buchhaltungsabteilungen eingehende Rechnungen immer noch anhand von Bestellungen, Vereinbarungen oder internen Geschäftsregeln validieren. Elektronische Rechnungen, die nur in einem maschinenlesbaren Format wie XML oder JSON und ohne visuelle Darstellung versandt werden, stellen ein Hindernis für die Benutzerfreundlichkeit dar. <strong>Fehlerbehandlung</strong>  Oftmals ist unklar, wie Fehler in der erhaltenen elektronischen Rechnung zwischen Käufer und Verkäufer effizient gehandhabt werden sollen.</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nachhaltigkeit</strong>  Die Umstellung von Papier auf elektronische Rechnungen trägt erheblich dazu bei, den ökologischen Fußabdruck von Unternehmen zu verringern, nicht nur durch die Reduzierung der Abholzung, sondern auch durch die erhebliche Verringerung der Ressourcen, die für die manuelle Bearbeitung von Rechnungen erforderlich sind.</td><td><strong>Neue Lösungen stellen sich der Herausforderung</strong>  Obwohl die Theorie hinter der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung wie der Traum eines jeden Automatisierungsteams klingt, sieht die Realität so aus, dass globale Unternehmen bedingt durch die Komplexität im Hinblick auf Vorschriften, Reifegrad, Einführung, Standards und Formate immer noch mit einer unübersichtlichen Realität zu kämpfen haben, die neue Lösungen erfordert.</td></tr></tbody></table><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/jssmedia/Project/Abbyy/Abbyy/Insights/Blog/A%20Guide%20to%20E-invoicing%20in%20Accounts%20Payable/guide-to-e-invoicing-accounts-payable-b-848x44.jpg"                      alt="guide-to-e-invoicing-accounts-payable-a-848x44"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713324&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVTV1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV TV Webcaster</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Ist-die-e-Rechnung-die-Antwort-auf-alle-Traume-von-der-Automatisierung-der-Rechnungsverarbeitung"><a href="#Ist-die-e-Rechnung-die-Antwort-auf-alle-Traume-von-der-Automatisierung-der-Rechnungsverarbeitung" class="headerlink" title="Ist die e-Rechnung die Antwort auf alle Träume von der Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung?"></a>Ist die e-Rechnung die Antwort auf alle Träume von der Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung?</h2><p>Auch wenn sich die Einführung der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung beschleunigt, darf nicht vergessen werden, dass sie je nach Land schrittweise eingeführt wird. </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.ey.com/en%5Fgl/tax-alerts/german-finance-ministry-releases-discussion-draft-on-pending-introduction-of-e-invoice" >Deutschland <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> hat die elektronische Rechnungsstellung für das öffentliche Beschaffungswesen eingeführt. Ab 1. Januar 2025 müssen Unternehmen den Empfang und Verarbeitung von e-Rechnungen ermöglichen. Ebenfalls ab dem 1. Januar 2025 sind Unternehmen mit Sitz in Deutschland verpflichtet e-Rechnungen auszustellen, allerdings mit Übergangsregelungen bis 2027. </p><p>In <a class="link"   href="https://www.ey.com/en%5Fgl/tax-alerts/france-revises-schedule-for-adopting-e-invoicing-reform" >Frankreich wird die elektronische Rechnungsstellung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> für große Unternehmen ab September 2026 verbindlich vorgeschrieben. Alle anderen Unternehmen müssen die Vorschriften ab September 2027 erfüllen. </p><p>In Spanien müssen Unternehmen mit einem Gesamtumsatz von 8 Millionen Euro oder mehr pro Jahr die Vorgabe ein Jahr nach Inkrafttreten der technischen Vorschriften für die elektronische Rechnungsstellung erfüllen. </p><p>Im <a class="link"   href="https://ec.europa.eu/digital-building-blocks/sites/display/DIGITAL/eInvoicing+in+the+United+Kingdom" >Vereinigten Königreich ist die elektronische Rechnungsstellung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> für B2B-Zahlungen nicht vorgeschrieben, wohl aber für Zahlungen an und von öffentlichen Stellen. </p><p>Da Regierungen auf der ganzen Welt als Katalysatoren für die Einführung von Lösungen zur elektronischen Rechnungsstellung fungieren, verändert sich die Landschaft rasch. Es wird erwartet, dass zukünftig erheblich weniger Rechnungen gescannt und per OCR gelesen werden, während die <a class="link"   href="https://www.billentis.com/assets/reports/The%5Feinvoicing%5Fjourney%5F2019-2025.pdf" >Anzahl der elektronischen Rechnungen mittelfristig um 10 bis 20 % pro Jahr zunehmen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> dürfte. </p><p>Obwohl die Theorie hinter der elektronischen Rechnungsstellung wie der Traum eines jeden Automatisierungsteams klingt, sieht die Realität so aus, dass globale Unternehmen bedingt durch die Komplexität im Hinblick auf Vorschriften, Reifegrad, Einführung, Standards und Formate immer noch mit einer unübersichtlichen Realität zu kämpfen haben, die neue Lösungen erfordert. </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=35038891&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.dupinout.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/DupInOut-New-Duplicate-Scan-Tab.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Die-Wahl-der-richtigen-Losung-zur-Automatisierung-der-Rechnungsverarbeitung-fur-Ihre-elektronische-Rechnungen"><a href="#Die-Wahl-der-richtigen-Losung-zur-Automatisierung-der-Rechnungsverarbeitung-fur-Ihre-elektronische-Rechnungen" class="headerlink" title="Die Wahl der richtigen Lösung zur Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung für Ihre elektronische Rechnungen"></a>Die Wahl der richtigen Lösung zur Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung für Ihre elektronische Rechnungen</h2><p>Das Fazit ist, dass die hybride <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Rechnungsautomatisierung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> in absehbarer Zukunft noch Bestand haben wird. Um diese Komplexität bewältigen zu können, sind speziell entwickelte <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >KI-Lösungen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> erforderlich, wie z. B. <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Intelligent Document Processing <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, die Daten aus Rechnungen jeder Art, jedes Formats und jeder Sprache intelligent analysieren, klassifizieren, erfassen und in einen einzigen strukturierten Datenstrom für das ERP-System verwandeln können. </p><p>Erfahren Sie <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >hier <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> mehr darüber, wie ABBYY die hybride Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung angeht. </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Demo anfordern <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><hr><p>* Einige der Dateiformate und Standards, die für den elektronischen Datenaustausch und die elektronische Rechnungsstellung verwendet werden, sind:</p><ul><li><strong>EDIFACT</strong> - wird international, insbesondere in Europa, für den elektronischen Datenaustausch verwendet.</li><li><strong>UBL (Universal Business Language) 2.0</strong> - die von der OASIS entwickelte UBL ist weit verbreitet und enthält neben Standards für Rechnungen auch Standards für verschiedene Geschäftsdokumente.</li><li><strong>ZUGFeRD</strong> - ein in Deutschland verbreitetes Format, das PDF- und XML-Daten für Rechnungen kombiniert.</li><li><strong>Facturae</strong> - der in Spanien verbindlich vorgeschriebene Standard für die Rechnungsstellung im öffentlichen Sektor.</li><li><strong>PEPPOL BIS Billing 3.0</strong> - wird vom PEPPOL-Netzwerk für grenzüberschreitende Transaktionen innerhalb Europas verwendet.</li><li><strong>eFFF (Electronic Flexible File Format)</strong> - in Belgien verwendetes Format, das verschiedene Arten von Geschäftsdokumenten unterstützt.</li><li><strong>Svefaktura</strong> - wird in Schweden insbesondere für Transaktionen mit dem öffentlichen Sektor verwendet.</li><li><strong>FatturaPA</strong> - das Standardformat für elektronische Rechnungen in Italien, speziell für Transaktionen der öffentlichen Verwaltung.</li><li><strong>ANSI X12</strong> - ein in Nordamerika weit verbreiteter Standard für EDI-Transaktionen, einschließlich Rechnungsstellung.</li></ul><hr><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25713/slavenahristova-99x99.png"                      alt="Slavena Hristova ABBYY"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.copernic.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=41033091&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.2checkout.com/images/merchant/8d30aa96e72440759f74bd2306c1fa3d/Copernic-2023-Affiliate-728x90-Advanced.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>Slavena Hristova</p><p>Director of Product Marketing, Vantage group at ABBYY</p><p>Slavena Hristova ist Direktorin für Produktmarketing, Vantage bei ABBYY. Hristova leitet das globale Produktmarketing für die ABBYY Vantage-Produktlinie. Sie verwaltet den gesamten Produktlebenszyklus, von der Definition der Marktanforderungen und der Entwicklung von Markteinführungsstrategien bis hin zu Vertriebsunterstützung und Schulungsangeboten für Vertriebspartner. Sie verfügt über langjährige Erfahrung im Produktmanagement und Marketing in den Bereichen Texterkennung, Informations- und Dokumentenmanagement. </p><p>Verbinden Sie sich mit Slavena auf <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/slavena-hristova-r%C3%B6%C3%9Fler-044aa05a/" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h4 id="Blog-Updates-abbonieren"><a href="#Blog-Updates-abbonieren" class="headerlink" title="Blog Updates abbonieren"></a>Blog Updates abbonieren</h4><p>Vorname*</p><p>E-Mail*</p><p>Land*</p><p>LandAfghanistanAland-InselnAlbanienAlgerienAmerikanisch-SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarktisAntigua und BarbudaArgentinienArmenienArubaAustralienÖsterreichAserbaidschanBahamasBahrainBangladeschBarbadosBelgienBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivienBonaireBosnien und HerzegowinaBotsuanaBouvetinselBrasilienBritisches Territorium im Indischen OzeanBritische JungferninselnBrunei DarussalamBulgarienBurkina FasoBurundiKambodschaKamerunKanadaCabo VerdeKaimaninselnZentralafrikanische RepublikTschadChileChinaWeihnachtsinselKokosinselnKolumbienKomorenRepublik KongoDemokratische Republik KongoCookinselnCosta RicaKroatienCuraçaoZypernTschechischeCôte d`IvoireDänemarkDschibutiDominicaDominikanische RepublikEcuadorÄgyptenEl SalvadorÄquatorialguineaEritreaEstlandÄthiopienFalklandinselnFäröerFidschiFinnlandFrankreichFranzösisch-GuayanaFranzösisch-PolynesienFranzösische SüdgebieteGabunGambiaGeorgienDeutschlandGhanaGibraltarGriechenlandGrönlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard und die McDonaldinselnVatikanstadtHondurasHongkongUngarnIslandIndienIndonesienIrakIrlandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaikaJapanJerseyJordanienKasachstanKeniaKiribatiSüdkoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLettlandLibanonLesothoLiberiaLibyenLiechtensteinLitauenLuxemburgMacauMazedonienMadagaskarMalawiMalaysiaMaledivenMaliMaltaMarshall-InselnMartiniqueMauretanienMauritiusMayotteMexikoMikronesienMoldawienMonacoMongoleiMontenegroMontserratMarokkoMosambikMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNiederlandeNiederländische AntillenNeukaledonienNeuseelandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolkinselNördliche MarianenNorwegenOmanPakistanPalauPalästinaPanamaPapua-NeuguineaParaguayPeruPhilippinenPitcairnPolenPortugalPuerto RicoKatarRumänienRuandaWiedervereinigungSt. HelenaSt. Kitts und NevisSt. LuciaSaint-Pierre und MiquelonSt. Vincent und die GrenadinenSaint-BarthélemySaint Martin (französischer Teil)SamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé und PríncipeSaudi-ArabienSenegalSerbienSeychellenSierra LeoneSingapurSt. MartinSlowakeiSlowenienSalomonenSüdafrikaSüdgeorgien und die Südlichen SandwichinselnSüdsudanSpanienSri LankaSurinameSpitzbergen (Norwegen)SwasilandSchwedenSchweizTaiwanTadschikistanTansaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad und TobagoTunesienTürkeiTurks- und CaicosinselnTuvaluUgandaUkraineVereinigte Arabische EmirateGroßbritannienUSAUruguayKleinere amerikanische ÜberseeinselnUsbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamAmerikanische JungferninselnWallis und FutunaWestsaharaSambiaSimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>Ich habe die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datenschutzerklärung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie-Richtlinie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gelesen und bin damit einverstanden.</p></li><li><p>Ich bin damit einverstanden, dass ABBYY Solutions Ltd. mich per E-Mail über Neuigkeiten zu Produkten und Technologien von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. informiert sowie Einladungen zu Veranstaltungen und Webinaren und Informationen über Whitepaper und Inhalte zu Produkten und Dienstleistungen von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. an mich sendet.</p></li></ul><p>Mir ist bekannt, dass ich meine Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen kann, indem ich auf den Link zur Abmeldung in einer von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. erhaltenen E-Mail klicke oder über das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datensubjekt-Zugriffsformular von ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Nachname</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Leveraging-Cookiebot-Solutions-Boosting-Online-Traffic-Conversion-Rates&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Leveraging-Cookiebot-Solutions-Boosting-Online-Tr</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Experience Tailored Navigation with Cookiebot Technology</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/experience-tailored-navigation-with-cookiebot-technology/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/experience-tailored-navigation-with-cookiebot-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.227Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.227Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Experience-Tailored-Navigation-with-Cookiebot-Technology"><a href="#Experience-Tailored-Navigation-with-Cookiebot-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Experience Tailored Navigation with Cookiebot Technology"></a>Experience Tailored Navigation with Cookiebot Technology</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to The Intelligent Enterprise <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Welcome-to-The-Intelligent-Enterprise"><a href="#Welcome-to-The-Intelligent-Enterprise" class="headerlink" title="Welcome to The Intelligent Enterprise"></a>Welcome to The Intelligent Enterprise</h2><h6 id=""><a href="#" class="headerlink" title=""></a></h6><p>by Ulf Persson  </p><p>Demand for IT in 2023 is expected to be strong as enterprises push forward with digital business initiatives in response to economic turmoil. Worldwide IT spending is projected to total $4.6 trillion in 2023, an increase of 5.1% from 2022, according to the latest forecast by Gartner, Inc.</p><p><em><a class="link"   href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2022-10-19-gartner-forecasts-worldwide-it-spending-to-grow-5-percent-in-2023" >Gartner Forecasts Worldwide IT Spending to Grow 5.1% in 2023 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, Oct. 19, 2022</em></p><p>Share</p><p>Just when we thought we heard enough of “unprecedented,” we again find our global markets experiencing new challenges.</p><p>But this time, company leaders are not so caught off guard as they were in 2020 by Covid-19 and are more prepared for the eventual economic downturn.</p><p>Still, many of the same challenges exist: volatile market conditions, reduced workforce, more demanding customer expectations, stricter budget controls, and increasing competition. The balancing act to appease investors, employees, and customers takes a more collaborative and intentional effort that is driving leaders to seek technology to digitally transform their business and augment their workforce.</p><p>However, there is a noticeable slowing in information technology (IT) decision-making. The haste during the pandemic to bypass standard sales cycles has left many organizations with technical debt and siloed solutions that haven’t made the impact promised. This has caused decision makers to untangle and reassess their automation solutions and be more prudent with future investments.</p><h3 id="How-AI-Identity-Proofing-Is-Transforming-Government-Services"><a href="#How-AI-Identity-Proofing-Is-Transforming-Government-Services" class="headerlink" title="How AI Identity Proofing Is Transforming Government Services"></a>How AI Identity Proofing Is Transforming Government Services</h3><p>eBook</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Download eBook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p>It’s for these reasons that we are debuting <strong><em>The Intelligent Enterprise</em></strong>, where each quarter we share our customers’ experiences and applicable insights to help your digital initiatives succeed faster. In this issue, we address common issues relating to augmenting full-time employees’ productivity, improving the customer experience, best practices from government agencies, and even how intelligent automation is making the world a safer place.</p><p>You’ll learn how Banner Health improved its claims processes and saved employees 2,100+ hours in administrative tasks, and results from a global survey revealing how more than 1,600 IT decision makers plan to improve onboarding. You’ll see how global organizations are hopeful, fearless, and are making their enterprises smarter.</p><p>In future issues of <em>The Intelligent Enterprise</em>, we’ll feature interviews with innovation and automation leaders who are transforming their organizations to improve how they work and make their customers’ lives better.</p><p>Threaded throughout, you’ll see how ABBYY transforms the content running through enterprise applications into knowledge that drives more intelligent decision-making and more powerful results faster–which are essential in today’s economic climate.</p><p>I encourage you to subscribe to The Intelligent Enterprise and learn about other <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >customers’ stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37001/ulf-persson_110x110-2.png"                      alt="Ulf Persson 110X110 (2)"                ></p><p>Ulf Persson</p><p>Chief Executive Officer at ABBYY</p><p>Ulf Persson has been a member of the ABBYY Group Board since 2002. In March 2015, Ulf became the Chairman of the Board. In 2017, he was appointed as the CEO of ABBYY Group.</p><p>Over the past 20 years, Ulf Persson has been involved as an investor and board member in about 20 different growth companies, including Tablogix (logistics services), jNetx (telecom software), Parallel Graphics (web3D software), Socialist Ltd (social media advertising), 2V Studios (TV content production), Elecsnet (payment services), UCMS (HR &amp; accounting BPO) and MyMoney (P2P car financing).</p><p>Follow Ulf on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ulf-persson-10085a79/" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.absolute.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4601998&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/ef70e26a0b5da778eda3f48014d087cd/728x90_larger-shield.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Additional-Insights"><a href="#Additional-Insights" class="headerlink" title="Additional Insights:"></a>Additional Insights:</h3><p>1 &#x2F; 3 </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37015/onboarding_875247286_848x444.jpg"                      alt="Top Reasons Why Customers Abandon Your Onboarding Processes...and How to Fix Them"                > <strong>Top Reasons Why Customers Abandon Your Onboarding Processes…and How to Fix Them</strong> Read more</a> <a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37014/government_1214434168_848x444.jpg"                      alt="How AI Can Help Government Agencies Win at Total Experience (TX)"                > <strong>How AI Can Help Government Agencies Win at Total Experience (TX)</strong> Read more</a> <a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36940/tlp_ia_orchestra_485765348_848x444.jpg"                      alt="Creating an Intelligent Automation Symphony"                > <strong>Creating an Intelligent Automation Symphony</strong> Read more</a> <a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37016/saferworld_863497498_848x444.jpg"                      alt="Document AI Creating a Safer World"                > <strong>Document AI Creating a Safer World</strong> Read more</a> <a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37013/fte_613347676_848x444.jpg"                      alt="Customer Point of View: Approach Automation Step by Step"                > <strong>Customer Point of View: Approach Automation Step by Step</strong> Read more</a> <a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37012/finance_1134322021_848x444.jpg"                      alt="The Changing Role of the Finance Leader"                > <strong>The Changing Role of the Finance Leader</strong> Read more</a> <a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36944/ai_happier_employees_1160730188_848x444.jpg"                      alt="Three Ways AI Is Making Employees Happier"                > <strong>Three Ways AI Is Making Employees Happier</strong> Read more</a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ancheer.sjv.io/c/5597632/1657301/17326" target="_top" id="1657301"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17326-1657301"                      border="0" alt="" width="1920" height="933"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1657301/17326"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Subscribe-for-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for updates"></a>Subscribe for updates</h4><p>Get updated on the latest insights and perspectives for business &amp; technology leaders</p><p>First name*</p><p>Last name</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Experience-Tailored-Navigation-with-Cookiebot-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Experience-Tailored-Navigation-with-Cookiebot-Technology&quot; class=</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Elevate Your Business with ABBYY FlexiCapture for a Digitally Advanced Future</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/elevate-your-business-with-abbyy-flexicapture-for-a-digitally-advanced-future/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/elevate-your-business-with-abbyy-flexicapture-for-a-digitally-advanced-future/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.217Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.217Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Elevate-Your-Business-with-ABBYY-FlexiCapture-for-a-Digitally-Advanced-Future"><a href="#Elevate-Your-Business-with-ABBYY-FlexiCapture-for-a-Digitally-Advanced-Future" class="headerlink" title="Elevate Your Business with ABBYY FlexiCapture for a Digitally Advanced Future"></a>Elevate Your Business with ABBYY FlexiCapture for a Digitally Advanced Future</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Government | Document Processing | Document Management</p><h2 id="ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Software-Helps-Companies-House-on-its-Journey-to-Becoming-a-Truly-Digital-Organisation"><a href="#ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Software-Helps-Companies-House-on-its-Journey-to-Becoming-a-Truly-Digital-Organisation" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY FlexiCapture Software Helps Companies House on its Journey to Becoming a Truly Digital Organisation"></a>ABBYY FlexiCapture Software Helps Companies House on its Journey to Becoming a Truly Digital Organisation</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/abbyy.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Software-Helps-Companies-House-on-its-Journey-to-Becoming-a-Truly-Digital-Organisation-1"><a href="#ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Software-Helps-Companies-House-on-its-Journey-to-Becoming-a-Truly-Digital-Organisation-1" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY FlexiCapture Software Helps Companies House on its Journey to Becoming a Truly Digital Organisation"></a>ABBYY FlexiCapture Software Helps Companies House on its Journey to Becoming a Truly Digital Organisation</h2><p>Government | Document Management </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15371/cs-companieshouse-556x303-2.jpg"                                     > </p><h4 id="Customer-Overview"><a href="#Customer-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Customer Overview"></a>Customer Overview</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"                      alt="Companies House"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>Companies House</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Headquarters</td><td>Cardiff, Wales</td></tr><tr><td>Industry</td><td>Public Sector</td></tr><tr><td>Products and Services</td><td>Making companies’ information available to the public</td></tr><tr><td>Web</td><td><a class="link"   href="http://www.companieshouse.gov.uk/" >www.companieshouse.gov.uk <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><h6 id="CHALLENGE"><a href="#CHALLENGE" class="headerlink" title="CHALLENGE"></a>CHALLENGE</h6><p>Slow, manual processing of physical documents</p><h6 id="SOLUTION"><a href="#SOLUTION" class="headerlink" title="SOLUTION"></a>SOLUTION</h6><p>Automated document and data processing with ABBYY FlexiCapture</p><h6 id="RESULTS"><a href="#RESULTS" class="headerlink" title="RESULTS"></a>RESULTS</h6><p>Digitised and streamlined document handling and routing</p><p>Companies House is an executive agency of the Department for Business Innovation and Skills. Its main role is to incorporate and dissolve limited companies, examine and store company information, and make this information available to the public. On average, around 5,000 sets of accounts are filed electronically with Companies House each day, and therefore automating document processes is crucial as it transforms into a fully digital organization.</p><h4 id="Challenge"><a href="#Challenge" class="headerlink" title="Challenge"></a>Challenge</h4><p>Companies House handles a large amount of paper on a daily basis. Whether that is filing an annual return, filing a company account or simply changing a company’s details, much of this information is still received in a paper-based format. As a result, this can cause bottlenecks, delays in responding and inefficiencies throughout the organization. Tackling this problem so that all documents are handled electronically became an important and strategic endeavour for Companies House.</p><h4 id="Have-a-task-Let’s-find-a-solution"><a href="#Have-a-task-Let’s-find-a-solution" class="headerlink" title="Have a task? Let’s find a solution"></a>Have a task? Let’s find a solution</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >CONTACT US <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Solution"><a href="#Solution" class="headerlink" title="Solution"></a>Solution</h4><p>Initially, Companies House looked at a number of different technology options, from developing the software from scratch internally to using applications from free libraries. The team also investigated other commercial offerings before settling on ABBYY. Ultimately, Companies House chose</p><p>ABBYY FlexiCapture Server to automate its paper-based business processes and reduce the high volume of paper it currently handles.</p><p> “ABBYY FlexiCapture provides a single entry point for us to automatically transform the stream of different forms and documents of any structure and complexity into business-ready data, which is easily integrated into our workflows.”</p><p> Carl Allen, Enterprise Architect at Companies House</p><p>“We needed a flexible solution that could easily integrate with our existing core systems and that gave a high recognition rate,” explained Allen. “The ABBYY solution came with various pre-built tools and utilities that allowed easy ‘zoning’ of the forms and the ability to define a template. This was the main reason why we chose to work with ABBYY.” </p><p>“We have also built an application for barcode identification to speed up the workflow process. Once a document is scanned into the system, the reader delegates the task to the appropriate department for handling, and archives the file on our servers, saving us both time and money by reducing admin-intensive tasks.”</p><h4 id="Results"><a href="#Results" class="headerlink" title="Results"></a>Results</h4><p>As a result of the integration, staff at Companies House are now able to extract data from forms and documents and directly embed the information into workflows to automate, separate and classify documents quickly. The FlexiCapture solution is particularly beneficial for large organizations such as Companies House, and other public sector bodies that work with huge volumes of documents. </p><p>The solution has provided a cost-effective way to process forms and put semi-structured and unstructured documents into one stream — including document classification, data verification and exporting for backend processing and archiving. It enables data capture to be integrated seamlessly into developer applications, so that full control is maintained over document processing, extracted data and document routing. “Initially, this was an experiment but the prototype of using the ABBYY FlexiCapture Server has been so successful, that we plan to continue to use it and expand the number and type of forms that we can process in this way,” explained Carl Allen. </p><p>“Of course the main benefit is that there is a greatly reduced volume of paper moving around the building. This is helping to reduce the amount of paper we handle, as we slowly ramp up the forms we process. We have deliberately operated a ‘creep and go’ process so that we can iron out any of the process is-sues on the business sections along the way, before we start processing all of the remaining paper,” he added.</p><p> ”We are pleased that Companies House has chosen ABBYY to power their solution. ABBYY award-winning forms processing and data capture end-user products are used by numerous government agencies and businesses all over the world and we’re looking forward to continuing the partnership in the future.”</p><p> Ed MacArthur, Head of Sales for ABBYY UK</p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/21380/4-flexicapture.jpg"                      alt="ABBYY FlexiCapture"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14361/11-government.jpg"                      alt="Government"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Government <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/1206/cs%5Fcompanies%5Fhouse%5Ffc%5Fe.pdf" title="PDF version"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15370/cs-companieshouse-360x162_2.jpg"                      alt="PDF Version"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/1206/cs%5Fcompanies%5Fhouse%5Ffc%5Fe.pdf"  title="PDF version">PDF version <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/1206/cs%5Fcompanies%5Fhouse%5Ffc%5Fe.pdf"  title="PDF version">read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h6 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h6><p>Share  True ?  : “” </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >More about ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Find your ABBYY office <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.movavi.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=MOVAVI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.movavi.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DMovavi%2BVideo%2BEditor%2Bbox"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://mcusercontent.com/0885a03ded3d480dca9287f12/images/6d3207fd-9f15-4c21-f0ad-59c68e6a7e2a.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to talk to an expert?"></a>Ready to talk to an expert?</h3><p>We’d love to help you along your automation journey.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Elevate-Your-Business-with-ABBYY-FlexiCapture-for-a-Digitally-Advanced-Future&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Elevate-Your-Business-with-ABBYY-FlexiCaptu</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Cutting Delivery Times for Global Top-Tier Brewery Karlstejn Group with Advanced ABBYY Systems</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/cutting-delivery-times-for-global-top-tier-brewery-karlstejn-group-with-advanced-abbyy-systems/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/cutting-delivery-times-for-global-top-tier-brewery-karlstejn-group-with-advanced-abbyy-systems/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.209Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.209Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Cutting-Delivery-Times-for-Global-Top-Tier-Brewery-Karlstejn-Group-with-Advanced-ABBYY-Systems"><a href="#Cutting-Delivery-Times-for-Global-Top-Tier-Brewery-Karlstejn-Group-with-Advanced-ABBYY-Systems" class="headerlink" title="Cutting Delivery Times for Global Top-Tier Brewery Karlstejn Group with Advanced ABBYY Systems"></a>Cutting Delivery Times for Global Top-Tier Brewery Karlstejn Group with Advanced ABBYY Systems</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Transportation &amp; Logistics | Food and Beverage | Forms Processing | Document Processing</p><h2 id="世界有数のビール会社-カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮"><a href="#世界有数のビール会社-カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮" class="headerlink" title="世界有数のビール会社 カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮"></a>世界有数のビール会社 カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/ja/183853.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >お客様のストーリーに戻る <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="世界有数のビール会社-カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮-1"><a href="#世界有数のビール会社-カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮-1" class="headerlink" title="世界有数のビール会社 カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮"></a>世界有数のビール会社 カールスバーグ・グループ、ABBYYのソリューションにより、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮</h2><p>食品および飲料 | 各種帳票処理／データキャプチャ </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36081/15063-carlsberg-556x303.png"                      alt="Costain Transforms Its Finance Department Using ABBYY Content Intelligence"                > </p><h4 id="お客様の概要"><a href="#お客様の概要" class="headerlink" title="お客様の概要"></a>お客様の概要</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36017/15064-logo-carlsberg-group.png"                      alt="Carlsberg Group"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>氏名</th><th>Carlsberg Group</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>本社</td><td>Copenhagen, Denmark</td></tr><tr><td>業界・業種</td><td>Breweries</td></tr><tr><td>ウェブサイト</td><td><a class="link"   href="https://www.carlsberggroup.com/" >www.carlsberggroup.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><p>ビール業界において世界を率いるグループ会社「Carlsberg（カールスバーグ）」は、製品を出荷するまでの時間を短縮し、顧客満足度を高めるための、受注・配送プロセスにおけるインテリジェントなソリューションを模索していました。そこでカールスバーグ・グループ（以下、カールスバーグ）は、ABBYYのインテリジェント文書処理（IDP）プラットフォームを活用し、注文と配送のプロセスをデジタル化することに成功いたしました。</p><h6 id="チャレンジ"><a href="#チャレンジ" class="headerlink" title="チャレンジ"></a>チャレンジ</h6><p>以前はメールで受け取った注文を社員が手動でシステムに入力</p><h6 id="ソリューション"><a href="#ソリューション" class="headerlink" title="ソリューション"></a>ソリューション</h6><p>受注データを自動で取り込むために、ABBYYのIDP技術を導入</p><h6 id="結果"><a href="#結果" class="headerlink" title="結果"></a>結果</h6><p>人が関わらない注文処理率が92％に。さらに月間140時間以上もの時間短縮を実現</p><p> ABBYYは、卓越した実務遂行戦略を掲げる当社を支え、当社のデータとプロセスをデジタルで把握することを可能にしてくれました。</p><p> カールスバーグのビジネス オーナー カミル・クロパツェフスキ氏</p><h4 id="チャレンジ-1"><a href="#チャレンジ-1" class="headerlink" title="チャレンジ"></a>チャレンジ</h4><p>カールスバーグは、多くの注文をメールで受け取っており、以前は社員がその注文情報をチェックして手動でシステムに入力していました。また、商品の配送手続きも手作業が多く、手入力されたファイルをSAPに取り込んでから商品受領書類を作成し、郵送していました。</p><h4 id="タスクがありますか？-解決策を見つけましょう"><a href="#タスクがありますか？-解決策を見つけましょう" class="headerlink" title="タスクがありますか？ 解決策を見つけましょう"></a>タスクがありますか？ 解決策を見つけましょう</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >お問い合わせ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="ソリューション-1"><a href="#ソリューション-1" class="headerlink" title="ソリューション"></a>ソリューション</h4><p>ABBYYのIDP技術をグローバルな受注プロセスに導入したことで、カールスバーグは送られてくる注文を自動的に取り込み、そのデータを即座に同社のSAPシステムに転送することができるようになりました。これにより、手作業による時間が大幅に削減されました。</p><p>ABBYYのIDPソリューションを納品書のスキャンプロセスに導入したことで、登録プロセス全体を自動的に処理することが可能になりました。入荷した商品の受け渡しや、ベンダーラベルの再利用などのプロセスが大幅に加速し、配送プロセス全体をより効率的に把握できるようになりました。</p><h4 id="価値"><a href="#価値" class="headerlink" title="価値"></a>価値</h4><ul><li>チームの生産性を向上させ、毎月140時間以上を削減</li><li>インテリジェント・オートメーションにより人が介在しない注文処理率が92％に</li><li>納期を早め、顧客満足度の向上を実現</li></ul><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/21380/4-flexicapture.jpg"                      alt="ABBYY FlexiCapture"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >詳細を読む <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/24337/mailroom_automation_360x162.jpg"                      alt="Learn more about ABBYY Vantage"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Vantage <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >詳細を読む <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36785/carlsberg-group-breweries-case-study-ja.pdf" title="PDF版"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36083/15063-carlsberg-360x162.png"                      alt="Download the PDF version"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36785/carlsberg-group-breweries-case-study-ja.pdf"  title="PDF版">PDF版 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36785/carlsberg-group-breweries-case-study-ja.pdf"  title="PDF版">資料を読む <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >More about ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Find your ABBYY office <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.mondly.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=ATISTUDI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mondly.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3D%2BEducational%2B300x600%2B"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/69c418c33ec2e1a4267fa9bb77fa1428/educational-300x600.gif"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to talk to an expert?"></a>Ready to talk to an expert?</h3><p>We’d love to help you along your automation journey.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Cutting-Delivery-Times-for-Global-Top-Tier-Brewery-Karlstejn-Group-with-Advanced-ABBYY-Systems&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Cutting-Delivery-Times-for</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Cookiebot: Your Gateway to Enhanced Web Analytics and Personalized Marketing</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/cookiebot-your-gateway-to-enhanced-web-analytics-and-personalized-marketing/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/cookiebot-your-gateway-to-enhanced-web-analytics-and-personalized-marketing/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.204Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.204Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Cookiebot-Your-Gateway-to-Enhanced-Web-Analytics-and-Personalized-Marketing"><a href="#Cookiebot-Your-Gateway-to-Enhanced-Web-Analytics-and-Personalized-Marketing" class="headerlink" title="Cookiebot: Your Gateway to Enhanced Web Analytics and Personalized Marketing"></a>Cookiebot: Your Gateway to Enhanced Web Analytics and Personalized Marketing</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Putting-Automated-Document-Processing-Into-Action"><a href="#Putting-Automated-Document-Processing-Into-Action" class="headerlink" title="Putting Automated Document Processing Into Action"></a>Putting Automated Document Processing Into Action</h2><p>December 21, 2017</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25256/8921e_smm_kryonsystems_blog.png"                      alt="Kryon Systems AI-based solution of choice is ABBYY FlexiCapture | ABBYY Blog Post"                > </p><p>As Artificial Intelligence continues to shape and accelerate the way we handle information and process data, it is also helping innovation-focused companies to use new AI-infused capabilities to improve business outcomes. One example is the Tel Aviv-based Kryon Systems, a global provider of intelligent Robotic Process Automation (RPA) solution. Kryon Systems recently decided to combine AI-powered document automation technology with its RPA solutions to create a single platform for document automation and streamline invoice and purchase order processing.</p><p>Kryon Systems AI-based solution of choice is ABBYY FlexiCapture, a top-of-the-line platform for automated processing of unstructured documents. By integrating FlexiCapture into its Leo RPA platform, the company will be able to offer businesses best-in-class RPA services that include the ability to parse unstructured data for invoice and purchase order processing.</p><p>Digital transformation is leading companies to turn to automation technologies in order to reduce errors, increase efficiency and boost profits across the enterprise. Kryon Systems’ RPA solution provides a workforce of “digital employees” onto whom crucial yet repetitive and time-consuming processes can be offloaded, enabling employees to devote more attention to higher value tasks that more directly contribute to the core mission of the company.</p><p>Traditionally, unstructured documents such as invoices and purchase orders, which lack standardized formats and are submitted as PDFs or scanned documents that cannot be edited, have posed an obstacle to automation efforts. By leveraging ABBYY, whose market-leading AI-powered document automation technology transforms unstructured documents into standardized files and alerts the relevant party when it is unable to do so, Kryon Systems is removing the hurdle which previously prevented the automation of these processes.</p><p>Industry leaders increasingly see cognitive solutions like ABBYY FlexiCapture as the future of enterprise capture platform for processing documents. “The needs of enterprises are evolving all the time, and we are constantly expanding the capabilities of our RPA platform to ensure that we provide a one-stop-shop automation solution for companies, no matter what processes they are seeking to optimize,” <a class="link"   href="http://www.kryonsystems.com/kryon-systems-leverages-abbyy-flexicapture/" >said Harel Tayeb, CEO of Kryon Systems <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. “Our new partnership with ABBYY allows us to help companies transcend the problem that unstructured invoices and purchase order forms cause by simply removing a substantial amount of time-consuming tasks from their employees’ workloads so they can focus on higher value assignments.”</p><p>The FlexiCapture platform will complement and extend the automation capabilities of Kryon RPA into document-based business processes, said Bruce Orcutt, SVP for Product Marketing at ABBYY. “Together, we look forward to helping clients address a full range of business process automation projects, from simple data entry, to more complex case automation,” he added.</p><p>ABBYY’s FlexiCapture platform is unique in being able to handle documents of any format, layout and structure thanks to its in-built, proprietary machine learning and natural language processing technology.</p><p>Invoices, which vary by supplier, are automatically read and processed, providing all necessary data to Kryon Systems’ Leo platform to execute the remainder of the process – checking and approval procedures, and posting to ERP systems for payment. Used in combination, both platforms automate and streamline document processes, driving operational efficiencies, reducing unnecessary costs and freeing up staff to focus on value-adding financial activities.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Digital Transformation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/artificial-intelligence-ai/"  title="Artificial Intelligence (AI)">Artificial Intelligence (AI) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/robotic-process-automation-rpa/"  title="Robotic Process Automation (RPA)">Robotic Process Automation (RPA) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/intelligent-document-processing-idp/"  title="Intelligent Document Processing (IDP)">Intelligent Document Processing (IDP) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4600113&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.epubor.com/images/drm-removal-feature2.png"                      border="0"                >Any DRM Removal for Win：Remove DRM from Adobe, Kindle, Sony eReader, Kobo, etc, read your ebooks anywhere.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Cookiebot-Your-Gateway-to-Enhanced-Web-Analytics-and-Personalized-Marketing&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Cookiebot-Your-Gateway-to-Enhanced-Web-Analyt</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Boost Your Site&#39;s Ranking with Advanced Cookiebot SEO Technology</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/boost-your-sites-ranking-with-advanced-cookiebot-seo-technology/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/boost-your-sites-ranking-with-advanced-cookiebot-seo-technology/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.196Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.196Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Boost-Your-Site’s-Ranking-with-Advanced-Cookiebot-SEO-Technology"><a href="#Boost-Your-Site’s-Ranking-with-Advanced-Cookiebot-SEO-Technology" class="headerlink" title="Boost Your Site’s Ranking with Advanced Cookiebot SEO Technology"></a>Boost Your Site’s Ranking with Advanced Cookiebot SEO Technology</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Actualités <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-optimise-la-technologie-de-Machine-Learning-de-sa-plateforme-FlexiCapture-pour-accroitre-ses-performances-de-traitement-des-contenus-d’entreprise"><a href="#ABBYY-optimise-la-technologie-de-Machine-Learning-de-sa-plateforme-FlexiCapture-pour-accroitre-ses-performances-de-traitement-des-contenus-d’entreprise" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY optimise la technologie de Machine Learning de sa plateforme FlexiCapture pour accroître ses performances de traitement des contenus d’entreprise"></a>ABBYY optimise la technologie de Machine Learning de sa plateforme FlexiCapture pour accroître ses performances de traitement des contenus d’entreprise</h2><p>07 novembre 2019</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><h4 id="De-formidables-gains-de-precision-a-la-cle-pour-la-plateforme-d’intelligence-des-contenus"><a href="#De-formidables-gains-de-precision-a-la-cle-pour-la-plateforme-d’intelligence-des-contenus" class="headerlink" title="De formidables gains de précision à la clé pour la plateforme d’intelligence des contenus"></a><em>De formidables gains de précision à la clé pour la plateforme d’intelligence des contenus</em></h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, le spécialiste de solutions d’intelligence digitale, annonce des gains de précision et de rapidité de traitement des contenus d’entreprise grâce à la technologie de machine learning (ML) de sa plateforme FlexiCapture 12. Cette plateforme unifiée de traitement intelligent des documents peut être déployée sur site, dans le cloud ou appelée par les développeurs au moyen d’un SDK ou d’API RESTful.</p><p>FlexiCapture s’adresse aux entreprises qui peinent à capturer et transformer les contenus non structurés des documents, formulaires et courriers, en données structurées signifiantes afin d’automatiser leurs opérations dans le cloud ou sur site. Tous les documents en lien avec les résultats et l’expérience client sont concernés : factures, réclamations, ouverture de compte, documents d’enregistrement de nouveau client, bons de commande, lettres de transport et contrats.</p><p>« Optimisée par les technologies de ML et IA, ABBYY FlexiCapture est la plateforme la plus complète, robuste et technologiquement avancée actuellement disponible en soutien des stratégies numériques des entreprises », commente Bruce Orcutt, vice-président senior en charge du marketing produit chez ABBYY. « Nos clients et partenaires traitent davantage de transactions plus rapidement, avec moins d’erreurs, ils améliorent le service client, réduisent les coûts et prennent de meilleures décisions. »</p><p>ABBYY teste également l’application à FlexiCapture de la technologie de traitement du langage naturel en vue d’étendre les fonctionnalités de capture aux documents non structurés. Les données non structurées seront ainsi plus faciles à comprendre, analyser et utiliser grâce à la structuration permise par la classification des contenus et l’extraction logique d’entités.</p><p>Selon <a class="link"   href="https://www.cognilytica.com/2019/05/28/white-paper-how-content-intelligence-will-transform-the-enterprise/"  title="Cognilytica">Cognilytica <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, jusqu’à 90% des contenus d’entreprise sont non structurés avec une progression de 65% par an. Les analystes prétendent que la plupart des données non structurées ne sont au final pas analysées et que l’on perd ainsi de précieuses informations faute de pouvoir les extraire facilement. Des tests réalisés en interne par ABBYY démontrent que, grâce aux technologies ML et IA, FlexiCapture 12.3 peut atteindre un degré de précision supérieur à 93% avant de transmettre les données à des solutions d’automatisation RPA (robotic process automation), solutions de gestion des processus métier (BPM) et moteurs de traitement des contenus.</p><p>Cette nouvelle version propose d’autres améliorations de performance :</p><ul><li>Gain de 50% du niveau de performance global de la plateforme FlexiCapture 12.3 pour les petits lots (3 à 5 pages) et de 10% pour les lots importants (100 pages)</li><li>Meilleure qualité d’extraction des données des factures grâce au réseau neuronal modernisé</li><li>Meilleurs taux d’extraction et meilleure qualité de traitement des tableaux complexes grâce à de nouvelles méthodes de machine learning</li></ul><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY est reconnu par Everest Group <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> comme un leader dans l’édition 2019 de son étude PEAK Matrix™ Assessment des produits IDP (Intelligent Document Processing) de traitement intelligent des documents. Pour Everest Group, IDP regroupe les logiciels ou solutions conçus pour capturer les données des documents, les catégoriser et extraire les données utiles, ensuite traitées au moyen de technologies IA.</p><p>« Nos investissements continus dans l’intégration de technologies IA à FlexiCapture afin d’améliorer les performances confortent notre position de leader du marché du traitement intelligent de documents », ajoute Bruce Orcutt.</p><p>Pour en savoir plus sur les caractéristiques du produit et ses applications possibles et savoir comment extraire de la valeur ajoutée des documents d’entreprise, visitez <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><strong>À propos d’ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY est un fournisseur international de solutions d’intelligence digitale. L’entreprise propose une gamme complète de technologies et de solutions basées sur l’intelligence artificielle qui permettent à la nouvelle « main-d’œuvre digitale » de mieux appréhender le contenu et les processus métier. Les technologies ABBYY sont utilisées et licenciées par des milliers d’entreprises internationales dans les secteurs de la finance, de l’assurance, du transport, de la santé et bien d’autres. Ce faisant, ABBYY aide les entreprises à prendre des décisions stratégiques plus pertinentes. ABBYY dispose d’une forte empreinte internationale avec 13 bureaux répartis dans le monde entier dont l’Australie, Chypre, France, Allemagne, Hong Kong, Hongrie, Japon, Russie, Espagne, Taiwan, Royaume-Uni, Ukraine et États-Unis. Pour plus d’informations, veuillez consulter le site <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/fr-fr/company/" >https://www.abbyy.com/fr-fr/company/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><strong>Contacts médias</strong></p><p>Eva-Maria Hufschmitt, ABBYY</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >eva-maria.hufschmitt@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Léonard Facchino &amp; François Aubert, Ballou France</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >abbyy@balloupr.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> &#x2F; 01 42 22 24 10</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.iobit.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4596923&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/184260348236f9554fe9375772ff966e/ascscan_468X60.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Boost-Your-Site’s-Ranking-with-Advanced-Cookiebot-SEO-Technology&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Boost-Your-Site’s-Ranking-with-Advanced-Cookiebot-SEO-Te</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>5-Schritte Für Die Erfolgreiche Implementierung Von RPA Mit ABBYY Prozessintelligenz - PDF</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/5-schritte-fur-die-erfolgreiche-implementierung-von-rpa-mit-abbyy-prozessintelligenz-pdf/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/5-schritte-fur-die-erfolgreiche-implementierung-von-rpa-mit-abbyy-prozessintelligenz-pdf/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.192Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.192Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="5-Schritte-Fur-Die-Erfolgreiche-Implementierung-Von-RPA-Mit-ABBYY-Prozessintelligenz-PDF"><a href="#5-Schritte-Fur-Die-Erfolgreiche-Implementierung-Von-RPA-Mit-ABBYY-Prozessintelligenz-PDF" class="headerlink" title="5-Schritte Für Die Erfolgreiche Implementierung Von RPA Mit ABBYY Prozessintelligenz - PDF"></a>5-Schritte Für Die Erfolgreiche Implementierung Von RPA Mit ABBYY Prozessintelligenz - PDF</h2><p>Broschüre</p><h2 id="In-5-Schritten-zum-Erfolgreichen-Einsatz-von-RPA-mit-Process-Intelligence"><a href="#In-5-Schritten-zum-Erfolgreichen-Einsatz-von-RPA-mit-Process-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="In 5 Schritten zum Erfolgreichen Einsatz von RPA mit Process Intelligence"></a>In 5 Schritten zum Erfolgreichen Einsatz von RPA mit Process Intelligence</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34492/10b-5-steps-to-successful-rpa-de-262x340.png"                      alt="In 5 Schritten zum erfolgreichen Einsatz von RPA mit Process Intelligence - ABBYY Broschüre"                ></p><h3 id="Wie-konnen-Sie-vor-dem-Hintergrund-dass-fast-die-Halfte-aller-RPA-Initiativen-gescheitert-sind-sicherstellen-dass-Sie-Erfolg-haben-werden"><a href="#Wie-konnen-Sie-vor-dem-Hintergrund-dass-fast-die-Halfte-aller-RPA-Initiativen-gescheitert-sind-sicherstellen-dass-Sie-Erfolg-haben-werden" class="headerlink" title="Wie können Sie vor dem Hintergrund, dass fast die Hälfte aller RPA-Initiativen gescheitert sind, sicherstellen, dass Sie Erfolg haben werden?"></a>Wie können Sie vor dem Hintergrund, dass fast die Hälfte aller RPA-Initiativen gescheitert sind, sicherstellen, dass Sie Erfolg haben werden?</h3><p>In dieser Broschüre erfahren Sie, warum der Erfolg von Projekten zur Robotic Process Automation nicht nur von Ihrem RPA-Anbieter abhängig ist. Für die Optimierung von Prozessen und Steigerung der Effizienz setzt sich die Automatisierung als Lösung zunehmend durch und Organisationen müssen eine Reihe von Faktoren berücksichtigen, wenn sie mit der Prozessautomatisierung beginnen.</p><p>Finden Sie heraus, wie die Stärken einer Process Intelligence-Plattform wie ABBYY Timeline Technologien für digitale Mitarbeiter ergänzen und die Prozessqualität sowie eine erfolgreiche Automatisierung mithilfe dieser fünf Best Practices sicherstellen.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2068407/7443" target="_top" id="2068407"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2068407"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2068407/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Jetzt-herunterladen"><a href="#Jetzt-herunterladen" class="headerlink" title="Jetzt herunterladen!"></a>Jetzt herunterladen!</h3><p>Steigern Sie Ihre Process Intelligence und machen Sie eine wirklich intelligente Automatisierung möglich</p><p>ABBYY Timeline bietet eine nahtlose RPA-Implementierung, die zu einem Re-Engineering der Geschäftsprozesse führt. Bei Ihren Initiativen zur digitalen Transformation sparen Sie dadurch nicht nur Zeit, sondern auch Geld.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=11224199&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/e09fdffe648a30658a9657bbed7b2388/products/copy_boxshot_lyricvideo.png"                      border="0"                >Lyric Video Creator Professional Version</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY"><a href="#Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY."></a>Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/documents/content/brochure-timeline-rpa-5-steps-to-success-de.pdf"  title="Broschüre lesen">Broschüre lesen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4599952&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><iframe width="864" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jVnfr5HudQw" title="The Latest and Easiest Solution to Remove Kindle DRM on Windows (without Degrading)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>Epubor Ultimate for Mac:Helps you read books anywhere, including the best eBook Converter + eBook DRM Removal functions.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns"><a href="#Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns" class="headerlink" title="Haben Sie Fragen? Kontaktieren Sie uns."></a>Haben Sie Fragen? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns. <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>Vorname*</p><p>Nachname*</p><p>E-Mail*</p><p>Land*</p><p>LandAfghanistanAland-InselnAlbanienAlgerienAmerikanisch-SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarktisAntigua und BarbudaArgentinienArmenienArubaAustralienÖsterreichAserbaidschanBahamasBahrainBangladeschBarbadosBelgienBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivienBonaireBosnien und HerzegowinaBotsuanaBouvetinselBrasilienBritisches Territorium im Indischen OzeanBritische JungferninselnBrunei DarussalamBulgarienBurkina FasoBurundiKambodschaKamerunKanadaCabo VerdeKaimaninselnZentralafrikanische RepublikTschadChileChinaWeihnachtsinselKokosinselnKolumbienKomorenRepublik KongoDemokratische Republik KongoCookinselnCosta RicaKroatienCuraçaoZypernTschechischeCôte d`IvoireDänemarkDschibutiDominicaDominikanische RepublikEcuadorÄgyptenEl SalvadorÄquatorialguineaEritreaEstlandÄthiopienFalklandinselnFäröerFidschiFinnlandFrankreichFranzösisch-GuayanaFranzösisch-PolynesienFranzösische SüdgebieteGabunGambiaGeorgienDeutschlandGhanaGibraltarGriechenlandGrönlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard und die McDonaldinselnVatikanstadtHondurasHongkongUngarnIslandIndienIndonesienIrakIrlandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaikaJapanJerseyJordanienKasachstanKeniaKiribatiSüdkoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLettlandLibanonLesothoLiberiaLibyenLiechtensteinLitauenLuxemburgMacauMazedonienMadagaskarMalawiMalaysiaMaledivenMaliMaltaMarshall-InselnMartiniqueMauretanienMauritiusMayotteMexikoMikronesienMoldawienMonacoMongoleiMontenegroMontserratMarokkoMosambikMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNiederlandeNiederländische AntillenNeukaledonienNeuseelandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolkinselNördliche MarianenNorwegenOmanPakistanPalauPalästinaPanamaPapua-NeuguineaParaguayPeruPhilippinenPitcairnPolenPortugalPuerto RicoKatarRumänienRuandaWiedervereinigungSt. HelenaSt. Kitts und NevisSt. LuciaSaint-Pierre und MiquelonSt. Vincent und die GrenadinenSaint-BarthélemySaint Martin (französischer Teil)SamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé und PríncipeSaudi-ArabienSenegalSerbienSeychellenSierra LeoneSingapurSt. MartinSlowakeiSlowenienSalomonenSüdafrikaSüdgeorgien und die Südlichen SandwichinselnSüdsudanSpanienSri LankaSurinameSpitzbergen (Norwegen)SwasilandSchwedenSchweizTaiwanTadschikistanTansaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad und TobagoTunesienTürkeiTurks- und CaicosinselnTuvaluUgandaUkraineVereinigte Arabische EmirateGroßbritannienUSAUruguayKleinere amerikanische ÜberseeinselnUsbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamAmerikanische JungferninselnWallis und FutunaWestsaharaSambiaSimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>Ich habe die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datenschutzerklärung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie-Richtlinie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gelesen und bin damit einverstanden.*</p></li><li><p>Ich bin damit einverstanden, dass ABBYY Solutions Ltd. mich per E-Mail über Neuigkeiten zu Produkten und Technologien von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. informiert sowie Einladungen zu Veranstaltungen und Webinaren und Informationen über Whitepaper und Inhalte zu Produkten und Dienstleistungen von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. an mich sendet.</p></li></ul><p>Mir ist bekannt, dass ich meine Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen kann, indem ich auf den Link zur Abmeldung in einer von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. erhaltenen E-Mail klicke oder über das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datensubjekt-Zugriffsformular von ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Anrede</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Stellen Sie eine Frage, oder beschreiben Sie Ihr Anliegen</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-Schritte-Fur-Die-Erfolgreiche-Implementierung-Von-RPA-Mit-ABBYY-Prozessintelligenz-PDF&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#5-Schritte-Fur-Die-Erfolgreiche-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Warum Fehlt Es Bei Deutschen Firmen Oftmals an Einem Verständnis Für RPA, Was Zu Misserfolgen Führt – Insights Von ABBYY</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/warum-fehlt-es-bei-deutschen-firmen-oftmals-an-einem-verstandnis-fur-rpa-was-zu-misserfolgen-fuhrt-insights-von-abbyy/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/warum-fehlt-es-bei-deutschen-firmen-oftmals-an-einem-verstandnis-fur-rpa-was-zu-misserfolgen-fuhrt-insights-von-abbyy/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.185Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.185Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Warum-Fehlt-Es-Bei-Deutschen-Firmen-Oftmals-an-Einem-Verstandnis-Fur-RPA-Was-Zu-Misserfolgen-Fuhrt-–-Insights-Von-ABBYY"><a href="#Warum-Fehlt-Es-Bei-Deutschen-Firmen-Oftmals-an-Einem-Verstandnis-Fur-RPA-Was-Zu-Misserfolgen-Fuhrt-–-Insights-Von-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Warum Fehlt Es Bei Deutschen Firmen Oftmals an Einem Verständnis Für RPA, Was Zu Misserfolgen Führt – Insights Von ABBYY"></a>Warum Fehlt Es Bei Deutschen Firmen Oftmals an Einem Verständnis Für RPA, Was Zu Misserfolgen Führt – Insights Von ABBYY</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="61-deutscher-Unternehmen-nennen-fehlendes-Prozessverstandnis-als-Grund-fur-RPA-Flops"><a href="#61-deutscher-Unternehmen-nennen-fehlendes-Prozessverstandnis-als-Grund-fur-RPA-Flops" class="headerlink" title="61% deutscher Unternehmen nennen fehlendes Prozessverständnis als Grund für RPA-Flops"></a>61% deutscher Unternehmen nennen fehlendes Prozessverständnis als Grund für RPA-Flops</h2><p>13. Mai 2020</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><h4 id="Eine-globale-Studie-von-ABBYY-zeigt-auf-welchem-Stand-Unternehmen-in-Sachen-RPA-und-Process-Mining-im-Jahr-2020-sind"><a href="#Eine-globale-Studie-von-ABBYY-zeigt-auf-welchem-Stand-Unternehmen-in-Sachen-RPA-und-Process-Mining-im-Jahr-2020-sind" class="headerlink" title="Eine globale Studie von ABBYY zeigt, auf welchem Stand Unternehmen in Sachen RPA und Process Mining im Jahr 2020 sind"></a><em>Eine globale Studie von ABBYY zeigt, auf welchem Stand Unternehmen in Sachen RPA und Process Mining im Jahr 2020 sind</em></h4><p>Eine kürzlich durchgeführte globale Studie von ABBYY ergab, dass das Verstehen der Unternehmensprozesse der primäre Erfolgsfaktor für Automatisierungsprojekte in deutschen Unternehmen ist. Im internationalen Vergleich ist zu sehen, dass Deutschland beim Einsatz von innovativen Technologien noch Schlusslicht ist.</p><p><strong>Deutsche Unternehmen sind sich des Mehrwerts von Process Mining bewusst</strong></p><p>Mehr als die Hälfte der Unternehmen (57%) gab an, dass sie bereits Technologien einsetzen, um zu verstehen, wie ihre Geschäftsprozesse genau ausgeführt werden, während weitere 23% der Entscheidungsträger angaben, in Zukunft Process-Mining-Technologien einsetzen zu wollen. Obwohl die Deutschen strikt ihre Prozesse befolgen – 92% der Entscheidungsträger gaben an, Mitarbeiter würden den Regeln entsprechend handeln – gestanden dennoch 89% der Befragten im Anschluss, dass es natürlich Ausnahmen gibt, bei denen Mitarbeiter von vorgefertigten Prozessen abweichen, wenn sie zu komplex sind oder für den Kunden angepasst werden müssen. </p><p>Deshalb sind mehr als zwei Drittel der Befragten auch vom Mehrwert dieser Technologien für ihr Unternehmen überzeugt: Sie gaben an, dass Process-Mining-Technologien die Funktionsweise von Prozessen sowie Verhaltensweisen analysieren können, um tiefere Einblicke zur Verbesserung der Prozesse zu gewinnen. Etwa genauso viele der Befragten nannten als wichtigsten Geschäftsnutzen, dass sie in Echtzeit über die Leistung der Prozesse informiert werden und Warnmeldungen erhalten, wenn Prozessregeln nicht eingehalten werden. Sogar ein Drittel gab an, dass Process-Mining-Technologien helfen, automatisch Probleme zu beheben (34%).</p><p><strong>Unternehmen sehen RPA als Businessbeschleuniger</strong></p><p>Die Umfrage zeigt auch, dass robotergesteuerte Prozessautomatisierung (RPA) in Unternehmen immer häufiger Anwendung findet. Fast zwei Drittel (64%) der Firmen in Deutschland setzen bereits RPA ein oder planen dies in den kommenden 12 Monaten zu tun. Bemerkenswert ist auch, dass Entscheidungsträger RPA nicht nur als Mittel für einfache, administrative Aufgaben sehen, sondern zunehmend den Wert für die Verbesserung geschäftskritischer Funktionen erkennen. Unternehmen in Deutschland sind der Meinung, dass RPA sowohl zur Verbesserung des Kundenerlebnisses beiträgt (38%), als auch im IT Service Management (38%) und bei der Finanzplanung (35%). Es zeigt sich, dass RPA-Integrationen auch bei immer komplizierteren Anwendungsfällen in Unternehmen eingesetzt werden, was sehr viel intelligentere komplementäre Technologien erfordert, um die Projekte erfolgreich durchzuführen. </p><p>| |  <strong>Finanzplanung und Entscheidungs-findung</strong> | <strong>Verbesserung des Kundenerlebnisses</strong> | <strong>IT Service Management</strong> | <strong>Optimierung im Onboarding-Prozess</strong> |     |<br>| ———————————————- | ————————————– | ————————- | ————————————- | — |<br>| <strong>Process mining</strong>                             | 55%                                    | 45%                       | 44%                                   | 42% |<br>| <strong>RPA</strong>                                        | 35%                                    | 38%                       | 38%                                   | 32% |</p><p><em>Tabelle 1: Befragung in Deutschland – “Wo erachten Sie den Einsatz von Process Mining&#x2F;RPA in Ihrem Unternehmen als sinnvoll?”</em></p><p><strong>Ohne Kenntnisse der genauen Prozesse ist RPA riskant</strong></p><p>Eines der wichtigsten Ergebnisse dieser Studie zeigt, dass ein ausgeprägtes Verständnis von Geschäftsprozessen für Automatisierungsinitiativen unerlässlich ist. Entscheidungsträgern in Deutschland zufolge bildete ein umfangreiches Verständnis jener Prozesse, die automatisiert wurden, den primären Erfolgsfaktor für die Umsetzung von RPA-Initiativen (61%). Es folgen Aspekte wie die präzise Planung von Projekten (52%) und professionelle Beratung von externer Stelle (42%).</p><p>Umgekehrt geben Unternehmen, die RPA-Misserfolge hinter sich hatten, folgendes als Hauptfaktoren an: unzureichende Unterstützung durch den RPA-Anbieter (46%), die Komplexität und zu hohe Variabilität von Prozessen (29%) ebenso wie die Tatsache, dass sich die externe Beratung als nicht hilfreich erwies (29%). Als RPA-Flop wurde von 51% der Fall genannt, dass der automatisierte Prozess ein höheres Maß an menschlicher Intervention erfordert als erwartet.</p><p>“Um Automatisierungsinitiativen erfolgreich durchzuführen, ist das Verständnis, wie Prozesse funktionieren und welche überhaupt automatisierbar sind, von essentieller Bedeutung. Mit innovativen Process-Mining-Technologien können Unternehmen Automatisierungspotenziale von Geschäftsprozessen identifizieren und diejenigen mit dem höchsten ROI-Potenzial priorisieren”, kommentierte Markus Pichler, VP Sales Europe von ABBYY. „Process-Intelligence-Tools sind unverzichtbar, um Unternehmen einen genauen Echtzeit-Überblick über ihre Prozesse zu verschaffen und aufzuzeigen, welche reibungslos funktionieren und noch wichtiger, welche eben nicht einwandfrei funktionieren und Engpässe schaffen. Nur mit dem notwendigen Grad an Prozesswissen sind Automatisierungsinitiativen erfolgreich. Prozesstechnologien werden zu einem Muss, da sie die digitale Transformation in deutschen Unternehmen wirkungsvoll vorantreiben können.” </p><p>Die Befragung wurde von ABBYY, einem globalen Anbieter von Technologien und Unternehmenslösungen für Digital Intelligence, in Auftrag gegeben und im März 2020 von Opinium Research durchgeführt. Dabei wurden 400 Entscheidungsträger in leitender Position aus Deutschland, Frankreich, Großbritannien und USA befragt, die in Organisationen aus den Bereichen Gesundheitswesen, Finanzdienstleistungen, Logistik und Transport sowie der Regierung tätig sind.</p><p>Um ein kostenloses Exemplar der Studie herunterzuladen, besuchen Sie bitte: <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/solutions/process-intelligence/research-report-2020/" >https://www.abbyy.com/solutions/process-intelligence/research-report-2020/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Weiterführende Informationen zu den Digital Intelligence-Lösungen von ABBYY finden Sie auf unserer Website: <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/" >https://www.abbyy.com/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><strong>Über ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY ist ein globaler Anbieter von Technologien und Unternehmenslösungen für Digital Intelligence. Die Digital Intelligence Plattform von ABBYY hilft Unternehmen, die gesamten Geschäftsprozesse zu verstehen und so ihren digitalen IQ zu erhöhen. ABBYY-Technologien werden von Fortune-500-Unternehmen aus dem Bankenwesen, der Versicherungsbranche, der Logistik, dem Gesundheitswesen und anderen Branchen eingesetzt, um intelligente Geschäftsentscheidungen zu treffen. ABBYY ist ein weltweit tätiges Unternehmen mit Niederlassungen in 13 Ländern. Weitere Informationen finden Sie unter <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.ABBYY.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY und das ABBYY Logo sind entweder registrierte Warenzeichen oder Warenzeichen von ABBYY Software Ltd. Alle anderen Warenzeichen sind Eigentum ihrer jeweiligen Inhaber.</em></p><p><strong>Pressekontakt</strong></p><p>Eva-Maria Hufschmitt, ABBYY<br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >eva-maria.hufschmitt@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4715391&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/7f687767ccf20fcea1c9dc4a5adc2326/Digisigner_banner_728_x_90_color_version.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Warum-Fehlt-Es-Bei-Deutschen-Firmen-Oftmals-an-Einem-Verstandnis-Fur-RPA-Was-Zu-Misserfolgen-Fuhrt-–-Insights-Von-ABBYY&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#W</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Verbessern Sie Die Sicherheit Von Dokumenten Bei Der Eingabe Mit Tangro® - Hochladen per Process Security</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/verbessern-sie-die-sicherheit-von-dokumenten-bei-der-eingabe-mit-tangro-hochladen-per-process-security/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/verbessern-sie-die-sicherheit-von-dokumenten-bei-der-eingabe-mit-tangro-hochladen-per-process-security/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.176Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.176Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Verbessern-Sie-Die-Sicherheit-Von-Dokumenten-Bei-Der-Eingabe-Mit-Tangro®-Hochladen-per-Process-Security"><a href="#Verbessern-Sie-Die-Sicherheit-Von-Dokumenten-Bei-Der-Eingabe-Mit-Tangro®-Hochladen-per-Process-Security" class="headerlink" title="Verbessern Sie Die Sicherheit Von Dokumenten Bei Der Eingabe Mit Tangro® - Hochladen per Process Security"></a>Verbessern Sie Die Sicherheit Von Dokumenten Bei Der Eingabe Mit Tangro® - Hochladen per Process Security</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="tangro®-erhoht-Prozess-Sicherheit-im-Dokumenteneingang-dank-ABBYY"><a href="#tangro®-erhoht-Prozess-Sicherheit-im-Dokumenteneingang-dank-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="tangro® erhöht Prozess-Sicherheit im Dokumenteneingang dank ABBYY"></a>tangro® erhöht Prozess-Sicherheit im Dokumenteneingang dank ABBYY</h2><p>10. Mai 2016</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><p>ABBYY Europe, ein führender Anbieter von Technologien und Lösungen für Dokumentenerkennung, Data Capture und Linguistik, erhöht die Ausfallsicherheit von Lösungen der tangro software components GmbH weiter. Der Hersteller von embedded SAP-Lösungen setzt bei seiner Software zur automatisierten Dokumentenverarbeitung schon lange auf die OCR-Technologie von ABBYY für die Dokumentendigitalisierung und Texterkennung (OCR). Diese ist die Basis für die Datenextraktion und die darauf folgende Verarbeitung in SAP. Dank der neuen Funktion ‚redundanter Netzwerk-Lizenz-Manager‘ im integrierten ABBYY OCR-Toolkit können Applikationen von tangro nun einen durchgängigen, ausfallsicheren Betrieb bei der Texterkennung im Dokumenteneingang sichern. Kunden von tangro gewinnen dadurch eine höhere Prozess- und Investitionssicherheit.</p><p>Die tangro software components GmbH ist ausgewiesener Experte für die automatisierte Verarbeitung eingehender Dokumente in SAP. Mit der tangro Inbound Suite bietet der Software-Hersteller eine Komplettlösung für die automatisierte Dokumenteneingangsverarbeitung, die SAP-embedded ist. tangro nutzt seit Jahren das Software Development Kit ABBYY FineReader Engine erfolgreich für die OCR-Komponente in der hauseigenen Lösung für die Belegverarbeitung. Je nach Kundenprojekt werden damit bis zu mehreren Tausend Dokumente pro Tag verarbeitet. Die integrierte ABBYY OCR-Technologie konvertiert Text in eingescannten Dokumenten in weiterverarbeitbare und strukturierte Daten, die dann an die entsprechenden SAP-Workflows übergeben werden. Dieser Arbeitsschritt ist wesentlich für die automatisierte Dokumenteneingangsverarbeitung. Ein Ausfall des Systems würde alle Folgeprozesse beeinträchtigen, zusätzliche Kosten für die Wiederherstellung des Systems verursachen und das Risiko von Datenverlusten erhöhen – vor allem bei hohen Dokumentenvolumen.</p><p>Um sicherzustellen, dass der OCR-Prozess nicht unterbrochen wird, werden immer häufiger mehrere OCR-Verarbeitungsstationen im Netzwerk genutzt. Darüber hinaus wurde nun zur Erhöhung der System-Verfügbarkeit das OCR SDK um das Feature ‚redundanter Netzwerk-Lizenz-Manager‘ erweitert. Die Netzwerk-Lizenz-Manager-Komponente wird dabei auf verschiedenen Hardware-Systemen in einer Cluster-Architektur installiert, die eine Back-up-Funktionalität sicherstellt und im Falle eines Ausfalls eines der Server für das Lizenz-Management den Betrieb der OCR-Software fortsetzt. Damit wird gewährleistet, dass der Prozess der Texterkennung auf den Workstations aufrechterhalten wird – und dass die gesamte Dokumentenverarbeitung zuverlässig und ausfallsicher abläuft.</p><p>„_Ein Ausfall des Lizenz-Servers ist zwar sehr selten, aber fatal – denn wenn die Texterkennung nicht mehr durchgeführt wird, kommt die ganze Dokumentenverarbeitung zum Stillstand. Mit dem redundanten Netzwerk-Lizenz-Manager können wir unseren Kunden Hochverfügbarkeit und eine hohe Prozess-Sicherheit bieten“, erklärt Dominik Pfizenmaier, Softwareentwickler bei der tangro software components GmbH. „Bei der Einführung wurden wir vom technischen Support-Team von ABBYY sehr gut begleitet. Wir haben die Lösung mit der neuen Funktion bereits in verschiedenen Projekten eingesetzt und sie funktioniert äußerst zuverlässig. Dank ABBYY können wir unseren Kunden die erforderliche Betriebssicherheit gewährleisten und so unsere Marktposition weiter stärken._“</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FineReader Engine <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gehört zur Produktlinie der Software Development Kits (SDKs). Diese ermöglichen Entwicklern, ABBYY Technologien für OCR und Dokumentenkonvertierung in Kundenanwendungen und Backend-Systeme von Unternehmen zu integrieren. Sie stehen für unterschiedlichste Plattformen zur Verfügung, darunter Windows, Linux, OS X, mobile Plattformen wie Android und iOS, aber auch als Cloud-OCR-Service mit API. Mehr Informationen zum Produkt und zur Möglichkeit, dieses kostenlos zu testen, finden Sie unter <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >http://www.abbyy.com/de-de/ocr-sdk/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h4 id="ABBYY-Europe-GmbH"><a href="#ABBYY-Europe-GmbH" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Europe GmbH"></a>ABBYY Europe GmbH</h4><p>ABBYY Europe ist ein Mitglied der ABBYY Gruppe und verantwortet Vertrieb und Marketing in Westeuropa. ABBYY ist ein führender Anbieter von Technologien für Dokumentenerkennung, Data Capture und Linguistik. Zum Produktportfolio gehören ABBYY FineReader Applikationen für OCR (Optical Character Recognition), ABBYY FlexiCapture Produktreihe für Data Capture, sowie Software Development Kits für Entwickler. ABBYY bietet Professional Services, um Kunden bei der Implementierung von Business Lösungen auf Basis der ABBYY Produkte zu unterstützen. Weltweit nutzen Unternehmen mit einem hohen Aufkommen an Papierdokumenten ABBYY Software zur Automatisierung zeit- und arbeitsintensiver Verarbeitungsaufgaben und zur effizienteren Gestaltung von Businessprozessen. Staatliche Institutionen setzen ABBYY-Produkte für großvolumige Projekte ein, darunter die Australische Steuerbehörde, die Litauische Steueraufsichtsbehörde, das Russische Bildungsministerium, das Ukrainische Bildungsministerium, die Regierung des Montgomery County in den Vereinigten Staaten und die Regierung von Kanada. Zu den Lizenznehmern der Erkennungs-Technologien von ABBYY zählen: BancTec, Canon, EMC&#x2F;Captiva, Hewlett-Packard, KnowledgeLake, Microsoft, NewSoft, Notable Solutions, Samsung Electronics, u.v.m. ABBYY-Applikationen werden weltweit zusammen mit Geräten führender Hersteller ausgeliefert, darunter Epson, Fujitsu, Fuji Xerox, Microtek, Panasonic, PFU, Plustek, Ricoh, Toshiba, und Xerox. ABBYY ist ein global tätiges Unternehmen mit regionalen Niederlassungen in Deutschland, Großbritannien, Frankreich, Spanien, den USA, Kanada, Ukraine, Zypern, Australien, Japan und Taiwan. Weitere Informationen über ABBYY finden sich im Web unter <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY, das ABBYY Logo, ADRT, FineReader, FlexiCapture und FlexiLayout sind entweder registrierte Warenzeichen oder Warenzeichen von ABBYY Software Ltd. Alle anderen Warenzeichen sind Eigentum ihrer jeweiligen Inhaber.</em></p><h4 id="Uber-die-tangro-software-components-gmbh"><a href="#Uber-die-tangro-software-components-gmbh" class="headerlink" title="Über die tangro software components gmbh"></a>Über die tangro software components gmbh</h4><p>Die tangro software components gmbh (<a class="link"   href="http://www.tangro.de/" >www.tangro.de <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>) ist SAP-Spezialist für Inbound Dokumenten Management mit über 30 Jahren SAP-Erfahrung. tangro unterstützt Unternehmen bei der Optimierung und Automatisierung ihrer Geschäftsprozesse im Dokumenteneingang für alle Eingangskanäle (Papier, Fax, E-Mail, EDI u.a.). Dank der patentierten Anwendungsarchitektur entwickelt tangro Software auf besonders effektive Weise und setzt individuelle Anforderungen schnell und kostengünstig um.</p><h4 id="Weitere-Information"><a href="#Weitere-Information" class="headerlink" title="Weitere Information:"></a>Weitere Information:</h4><p>ABBYY Europe GmbH<br>Christian Schwarzmann<br>Elsenheimerstraße 49<br>D - 80687 München<br>Tel.: +49 89 69 33 33 0<br>Fax: +49 89 69 33 33 300<br>E-Mail: press_<a class="link"   href="mailto:&#101;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#98;&#121;&#121;&#x2e;&#x63;&#x6f;&#x6d;" >&#101;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#98;&#121;&#121;&#x2e;&#x63;&#x6f;&#x6d; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Web: <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Pressekontakt:</p><p>LEWIS PR<br>Matthias Gröschel<br>Karlstr. 64<br>D - 80335 München<br>Tel.: +49 89 17 30 19 22<br>E-Mail: <a class="link"   href="mailto:&#x61;&#x62;&#98;&#x79;&#121;&#103;&#101;&#x72;&#109;&#x61;&#x6e;&#x79;&#64;&#116;&#101;&#x61;&#x6d;&#108;&#x65;&#119;&#105;&#x73;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109;" >&#x61;&#x62;&#98;&#x79;&#121;&#103;&#101;&#x72;&#109;&#x61;&#x6e;&#x79;&#64;&#116;&#101;&#x61;&#x6d;&#108;&#x65;&#119;&#105;&#x73;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://estore.winxdvd.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4612444&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.winxdvd.com/affiliate/new-banner/pt-728x90.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Verbessern-Sie-Die-Sicherheit-Von-Dokumenten-Bei-Der-Eingabe-Mit-Tangro®-Hochladen-per-Process-Security&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Verbessern-Sie-Di</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Untapped Opportunities: How British Enterprises Can Harness Automation Advantages, According to ABBYY Insights</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/untapped-opportunities-how-british-enterprises-can-harness-automation-advantages-according-to-abbyy-insights/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/untapped-opportunities-how-british-enterprises-can-harness-automation-advantages-according-to-abbyy-insights/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.168Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.168Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Untapped-Opportunities-How-British-Enterprises-Can-Harness-Automation-Advantages-According-to-ABBYY-Insights"><a href="#Untapped-Opportunities-How-British-Enterprises-Can-Harness-Automation-Advantages-According-to-ABBYY-Insights" class="headerlink" title="Untapped Opportunities: How British Enterprises Can Harness Automation Advantages, According to ABBYY Insights"></a>Untapped Opportunities: How British Enterprises Can Harness Automation Advantages, According to ABBYY Insights</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="British-businesses-miss-out-on-ROI-of-automation-as-only-1-in-4-invest-in-RPA"><a href="#British-businesses-miss-out-on-ROI-of-automation-as-only-1-in-4-invest-in-RPA" class="headerlink" title="British businesses miss out on ROI of automation, as only 1 in 4 invest in RPA"></a>British businesses miss out on ROI of automation, as only 1 in 4 invest in RPA</h2><p>December 04, 2019</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><h4 id="•-This-comes-despite-over-80-of-businesses-seeing-ROI-on-RPA-within-a-year"><a href="#•-This-comes-despite-over-80-of-businesses-seeing-ROI-on-RPA-within-a-year" class="headerlink" title="• This comes despite over 80% of businesses seeing ROI on RPA within a year"></a><em>• This comes despite over 80% of businesses seeing ROI on RPA within a year</em></h4><h4 id="•-Combining-complementary-tech-behind-revenue-growth-for-71-of-UK-businesses"><a href="#•-Combining-complementary-tech-behind-revenue-growth-for-71-of-UK-businesses" class="headerlink" title="• Combining complementary tech behind revenue growth for 71% of UK businesses"></a><em>• Combining complementary tech behind revenue growth for 71% of UK businesses</em></h4><h4 id="•-Banking-and-FS-the-industry-leading-RPA-adoption-with-legal-profession-in-last-place"><a href="#•-Banking-and-FS-the-industry-leading-RPA-adoption-with-legal-profession-in-last-place" class="headerlink" title="• Banking and FS the industry leading RPA adoption, with legal profession in last place"></a><em>• Banking and FS the industry leading RPA adoption, with legal profession in last place</em></h4><p>British businesses are missing out on the benefits of automation by not combining the right technologies, recent research from Digital IQ provider ABBYY has found. While 19 in 20 businesses have deployed some form of automation, only 1 in 20 use the full stack, meaning most businesses are missing out on the ‘secret weapons’ that could deliver the most ROI for their business.</p><p>While automated systems and AI come out as the most popular forms of automation, RPA is the least adopted, with only 24% of UK businesses investing in the technology. However, RPA is bringing unparalleled benefits. RPA is particularly strong on time to ROI – 82% of businesses saw a return on their RPA investment within a year, with 30% seeing a return of at least twice what they invested.</p><p>The banking &amp; FS sector leads the way, with 38% of businesses investing in RPA, while manufacturing comes in second place with 23%. Some sectors have barely dipped their toe, with the legal profession for example only seeing 6% adoption. This is despite the huge opportunities RPA brings: a majority of RPA adopters saw improved efficiency (55%), getting ahead of the competition&#x2F;increasing their market share (52%), and revenue growth (52%), with productivity gains (44%) and business transformation (40%) also realised.</p><p>The research also found that combining RPA with content-centric process automation drives even greater results, with 71% of businesses who have deployed both technologies growing their revenue – compared to just 37% for businesses who have invested just in RPA. This combination also led to improved productivity for 51% of businesses (vs. 39% of those using RPA without content-centric process automation) while 49% have achieved business transformation (vs. 33%) and 57% increasing their market share (vs 48%). Again banking and finance lead the way, with 35% of businesses deploying both technologies, compared to just 2% in the legal sector.</p><p>ABBYY is calling on large businesses to lead the charge for businesses to make the most of their automation investments. 4 in 5 large businesses (79%) have seen increased efficiency since implementing RPA, and 71% have become more productive. However, only 50% of businesses with more than 5,000 employees are using the tech, dropping to 36% for businesses with 500-4,999 employees. However, ABBYY customer Costain, which integrated ABBYY’s technology with RPA in an end-to-end solution – that can fetch an invoice, capture, identify and extract the essential data within it, then hand this over to the RPA bot to post an invoice into the ERP system – is seeing the benefit of deploying these technologies together.</p><p>“Collaborative work with ABBYY is part of our continued commitment to invest in technology to transform our finance function,” said Tony Bickerstaff, CFO at Costain. “We will continue to seek to use the latest technologies, including artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning, to make our business as efficient and competitive as possible,” he added.</p><p>“Using just one or two types of automation without integrating the tech that will help achieve your goals is at best short-sighted, and at worst a waste of time and money,” said Neil Murphy, Global VP at ABBYY. “The technologies that can drive enormous improvements for transaction-oriented processes across every sector – particularly in banking and finance and other heavily process-driven sectors – already exist. Some businesses simply don’t have the understanding on why their automation investments aren’t generating the ROI they hoped for. These businesses need to automate with RPA, but they also need to leverage the technology that can automate content-centric processes to make robots smarter with the introduction of new skills.”</p><p>“With the availability of more intelligent RPA solutions, such as attended automation, companies are in a unique position to leverage and benefit from automation in ways that were previously unavailable”, said Barry Cooper, President, NICE Enterprise Group. “Attended automation allows enterprises to scale the RPA footprint to tens of thousands of desktops, overcoming the current low footprint of unattended robots alone. With this combination, our own users are consistently unlocking benefits such as productivity gains, improvements in compliance adherence, growth in sales and superior customer experiences, all in a more rapid manner.”</p><p><strong>ABBYY Editorial Contacts:</strong></p><p>Eva-Maria Hufschmitt, ABBYY<br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >eva-maria.hufschmitt@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Gemma Sowerby and Archana Shah, LEWIS for ABBYY UK<br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >abbyyuk@teamlewis.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>0207 807 2626</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4599951&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><iframe width="864" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jVnfr5HudQw" title="The Latest and Easiest Solution to Remove Kindle DRM on Windows (without Degrading)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br>Epubor Ultimate for Win：Helps you read books anywhere, including the best eBook Converter + eBook DRM Removal functions.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Untapped-Opportunities-How-British-Enterprises-Can-Harness-Automation-Advantages-According-to-ABBYY-Insights&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Untapped-Opp</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Unleash Potential with Our Cookiebot Integrated Services</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/unleash-potential-with-our-cookiebot-integrated-services/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/unleash-potential-with-our-cookiebot-integrated-services/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.160Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.160Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Unleash-Potential-with-Our-Cookiebot-Integrated-Services"><a href="#Unleash-Potential-with-Our-Cookiebot-Integrated-Services" class="headerlink" title="Unleash Potential with Our Cookiebot Integrated Services"></a>Unleash Potential with Our Cookiebot Integrated Services</h2><p>Broschüre</p><h2 id="Einfache-Erfassung-Kontrolle-und-Verwaltung-Ihrer-Ausgaben"><a href="#Einfache-Erfassung-Kontrolle-und-Verwaltung-Ihrer-Ausgaben" class="headerlink" title="Einfache Erfassung, Kontrolle und Verwaltung Ihrer Ausgaben"></a>Einfache Erfassung, Kontrolle und Verwaltung Ihrer Ausgaben</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35132/77b-capture-track-and-manage-expenses-the-easy-way-de-262x340.png"                      alt="Capture, Track, and Manage Expenses the Easy Way - ABBYY Brochure"                ></p><h3 id="Eliminieren-Sie-die-manuelle-Verarbeitung-von-Belegen-durch-eine-intelligente-Dokumenten­verarbeitung"><a href="#Eliminieren-Sie-die-manuelle-Verarbeitung-von-Belegen-durch-eine-intelligente-Dokumenten­verarbeitung" class="headerlink" title="Eliminieren Sie die manuelle Verarbeitung von Belegen durch eine intelligente Dokumenten­verarbeitung"></a>Eliminieren Sie die manuelle Verarbeitung von Belegen durch eine intelligente Dokumenten­verarbeitung</h3><p>Verschwenden Sie keine wertvolle Zeit und Ressourcen für die Verarbeitung von Belegen. Wenn Spesenbelege manuell bearbeitet werden, führt das immer wieder zu Fehlern wie doppelten Zahlungen, zu Verzögerungen von Prüfungen und zu einem höheren Betrugsrisiko. Die Spesenmanagementlösung von ABBYY verschlankt und optimiert Ihre Erstattungsprozesse. Es handelt sich hier um eine betriebsbereite Software-Lösung, die Belege automatisch verarbeitet und die wertvollen Daten, die Sie für ein korrektes Spesenmanagement benötigen, automatisch extrahiert.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4550420&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.pearlmountainsoft.com/n_img/product/pic/f_02.jpg"                      border="0"                >PearlMountain Image Converter</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Jetzt-herunterladen"><a href="#Jetzt-herunterladen" class="headerlink" title="Jetzt herunterladen!"></a>Jetzt herunterladen!</h3><p>Laden Sie unsere Broschüre herunter und erfahren Sie, wie die intelligente Dokumentenverarbeitungslösung von ABBYY Ihnen helfen kann, Spesen auf ganz einfache Weise zu erfassen, nachzuverfolgen und zu verwalten:</p><ul><li>Einfache Nachverfolgung</li><li>Schnelle Berichtserstellung</li><li>Automatisierte Richtlinienkonformität</li><li>Nahtlose Integration in Buchhaltung &amp; ERP</li><li>Absolute Kontrolle über Budget-Ausgaben</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.movavi.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=MOVAVI&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.movavi.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DMovavi%2BVideo%2BEditor%2Bbox"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://mcusercontent.com/0885a03ded3d480dca9287f12/images/6d3207fd-9f15-4c21-f0ad-59c68e6a7e2a.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY"><a href="#Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY."></a>Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/documents/content/brochure-ap-expense-management-de.pdf"  title="Broschüre lesen">Broschüre lesen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2075475/7443" target="_top" id="2075475"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2075475"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2075475/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns"><a href="#Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns" class="headerlink" title="Haben Sie Fragen? Kontaktieren Sie uns."></a>Haben Sie Fragen? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns. <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>Vorname*</p><p>Nachname*</p><p>E-Mail*</p><p>Land*</p><p>LandAfghanistanAland-InselnAlbanienAlgerienAmerikanisch-SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarktisAntigua und BarbudaArgentinienArmenienArubaAustralienÖsterreichAserbaidschanBahamasBahrainBangladeschBarbadosBelgienBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivienBonaireBosnien und HerzegowinaBotsuanaBouvetinselBrasilienBritisches Territorium im Indischen OzeanBritische JungferninselnBrunei DarussalamBulgarienBurkina FasoBurundiKambodschaKamerunKanadaCabo VerdeKaimaninselnZentralafrikanische RepublikTschadChileChinaWeihnachtsinselKokosinselnKolumbienKomorenRepublik KongoDemokratische Republik KongoCookinselnCosta RicaKroatienCuraçaoZypernTschechischeCôte d`IvoireDänemarkDschibutiDominicaDominikanische RepublikEcuadorÄgyptenEl SalvadorÄquatorialguineaEritreaEstlandÄthiopienFalklandinselnFäröerFidschiFinnlandFrankreichFranzösisch-GuayanaFranzösisch-PolynesienFranzösische SüdgebieteGabunGambiaGeorgienDeutschlandGhanaGibraltarGriechenlandGrönlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard und die McDonaldinselnVatikanstadtHondurasHongkongUngarnIslandIndienIndonesienIrakIrlandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaikaJapanJerseyJordanienKasachstanKeniaKiribatiSüdkoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLettlandLibanonLesothoLiberiaLibyenLiechtensteinLitauenLuxemburgMacauMazedonienMadagaskarMalawiMalaysiaMaledivenMaliMaltaMarshall-InselnMartiniqueMauretanienMauritiusMayotteMexikoMikronesienMoldawienMonacoMongoleiMontenegroMontserratMarokkoMosambikMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNiederlandeNiederländische AntillenNeukaledonienNeuseelandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolkinselNördliche MarianenNorwegenOmanPakistanPalauPalästinaPanamaPapua-NeuguineaParaguayPeruPhilippinenPitcairnPolenPortugalPuerto RicoKatarRumänienRuandaWiedervereinigungSt. HelenaSt. Kitts und NevisSt. LuciaSaint-Pierre und MiquelonSt. Vincent und die GrenadinenSaint-BarthélemySaint Martin (französischer Teil)SamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé und PríncipeSaudi-ArabienSenegalSerbienSeychellenSierra LeoneSingapurSt. MartinSlowakeiSlowenienSalomonenSüdafrikaSüdgeorgien und die Südlichen SandwichinselnSüdsudanSpanienSri LankaSurinameSpitzbergen (Norwegen)SwasilandSchwedenSchweizTaiwanTadschikistanTansaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad und TobagoTunesienTürkeiTurks- und CaicosinselnTuvaluUgandaUkraineVereinigte Arabische EmirateGroßbritannienUSAUruguayKleinere amerikanische ÜberseeinselnUsbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamAmerikanische JungferninselnWallis und FutunaWestsaharaSambiaSimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>Ich habe die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datenschutzerklärung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie-Richtlinie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gelesen und bin damit einverstanden.*</p></li><li><p>Ich bin damit einverstanden, dass ABBYY Solutions Ltd. mich per E-Mail über Neuigkeiten zu Produkten und Technologien von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. informiert sowie Einladungen zu Veranstaltungen und Webinaren und Informationen über Whitepaper und Inhalte zu Produkten und Dienstleistungen von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. an mich sendet.</p></li></ul><p>Mir ist bekannt, dass ich meine Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen kann, indem ich auf den Link zur Abmeldung in einer von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. erhaltenen E-Mail klicke oder über das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datensubjekt-Zugriffsformular von ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Anrede</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Stellen Sie eine Frage, oder beschreiben Sie Ihr Anliegen</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Unleash-Potential-with-Our-Cookiebot-Integrated-Services&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Unleash-Potential-with-Our-Cookiebot-Integrated-Services&quot; class=</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Texthelp Und ABBYY: Revolutionärer Support Für Menschen Mit Leseschwäche Oder Dysgraphie</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/texthelp-und-abbyy-revolutionarer-support-fur-menschen-mit-leseschwache-oder-dysgraphie/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/texthelp-und-abbyy-revolutionarer-support-fur-menschen-mit-leseschwache-oder-dysgraphie/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.154Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.154Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Texthelp-Und-ABBYY-Revolutionarer-Support-Fur-Menschen-Mit-Leseschwache-Oder-Dysgraphie"><a href="#Texthelp-Und-ABBYY-Revolutionarer-Support-Fur-Menschen-Mit-Leseschwache-Oder-Dysgraphie" class="headerlink" title="Texthelp Und ABBYY: Revolutionärer Support Für Menschen Mit Leseschwäche Oder Dysgraphie"></a>Texthelp Und ABBYY: Revolutionärer Support Für Menschen Mit Leseschwäche Oder Dysgraphie</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Zurück zu den Kundenreferenzen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Education | Hardware &amp; Software | PDF and Document Conversion</p><h2 id="Texthelp-Systems-erleichtert-Menschen-mit-Lese-oder-Schreibschwachen-den-Zugang-zu-Informationen"><a href="#Texthelp-Systems-erleichtert-Menschen-mit-Lese-oder-Schreibschwachen-den-Zugang-zu-Informationen" class="headerlink" title="Texthelp Systems erleichtert Menschen mit Lese- oder Schreibschwächen den Zugang zu Informationen"></a>Texthelp Systems erleichtert Menschen mit Lese- oder Schreibschwächen den Zugang zu Informationen</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/de/70312.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Zurück zu den Kundenreferenzen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Texthelp-Systems-erleichtert-Menschen-mit-Lese-oder-Schreibschwachen-den-Zugang-zu-Informationen-1"><a href="#Texthelp-Systems-erleichtert-Menschen-mit-Lese-oder-Schreibschwachen-den-Zugang-zu-Informationen-1" class="headerlink" title="Texthelp Systems erleichtert Menschen mit Lese- oder Schreibschwächen den Zugang zu Informationen"></a>Texthelp Systems erleichtert Menschen mit Lese- oder Schreibschwächen den Zugang zu Informationen</h2><p>Bildungswesen | PDF- und Dokumentenumwandlung </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15362/cs-texthelp-556x303.jpg"                                     > </p><h4 id="Uber-den-Kunden"><a href="#Uber-den-Kunden" class="headerlink" title="Über den Kunden"></a>Über den Kunden</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14895/texthelp.png"                      alt="Texthelp Systems Ltd"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>Texthelp Systems Ltd</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Hauptsitz</td><td>Antrim, Nordirland</td></tr><tr><td>Branche</td><td>Assisted software solutions</td></tr><tr><td>Website</td><td><a class="link"   href="http://www.texthelp.com/" >www.texthelp.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><h6 id="Herausforderung"><a href="#Herausforderung" class="headerlink" title="Herausforderung"></a>Herausforderung</h6><p>Die Suche nach der genauesten OCR-Technologie für Windows und Mac-Plattformen zur Optimierunge der bestehnden Read&amp;Write software</p><h6 id="Losung"><a href="#Losung" class="headerlink" title="Lösung"></a>Lösung</h6><p>Implementierung von FineReader Engine in bestehende Software; dadurch neue Bilderkennung-, PDF-Konvertierungs- und Field-Level-Erkennungsoptionen</p><h6 id="Ergebnis"><a href="#Ergebnis" class="headerlink" title="Ergebnis"></a>Ergebnis</h6><ul><li>Erhöhte Erkennungsgenauigkeit</li><li>Leichte Integrierbarkeit in bestehende Systeme</li><li>Optimale Hilfestellung für SchülerInnen mit Lese- und&#x2F;oder Schreibschwächen beim Lesen von Internetseiten</li></ul><p>Read&amp;Write GOLD ist die Texthelp Lesehilfe Software für Schüler und Studenten aller Altersgruppen, die besondere Hilfe beim Lesen und Schreiben benötigen. Durch lautes Vorlesen von Texten hilft die Software Menschen mit Lernschwächen. Durch die Integration von ABBYY FineReader Engine kann Texthelp nun zum Nutzen seiner Kunden den Funktionsumfang von Read&amp;Write GOLD deutlich erweitern, denn dank der hohen Erkennungsqualität stehen den Nutzern mehr Informationen zur Verfügung.</p><h4 id="Hintergrund"><a href="#Hintergrund" class="headerlink" title="Hintergrund"></a>Hintergrund</h4><p>Nach Angaben der Organisation <a class="link"   href="http://www.dyslexiaaction.org.uk/" >www.dyslexiaaction.org.uk <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> haben zwischen 4 und 5 Prozent der britischen Bevölkerung Legasthenie. Das bedeutet, dass ungefähr 375.000 Schüler und insgesamt an die zwei Millionen Menschen in England aufgrund dieser Lese- und Rechtschreibschwäche (schriftliche) Informationen nur schwer erkennen und verwerten können. Die Texthelp Software Read&amp;Write GOLD hilft den Anwendern dabei, Texte zu lesen, zu schreiben oder zusammen zu setzen. Mithilfe der Erkennung von Bildschirmabbildungen (sog. Screenshots) können sich die Nutzer schwer zugänglichen Text auf Webseiten laut vorlesen lassen. Die Software verfügt über Hilfsfunktionen, die den meisten MS Windows Standardprogrammen fehlen. Zusätzlich bietet Read&amp;Write GOLD eine Vielzahl von Funktionen für Recherche und Satzbau. Schon die Möglichkeit, sich das Geschriebene nochmals vorlesen zu lassen ist eine perfekte Hilfe bei der Recherche und beim Korrekturlesen – sogar der integrierte Rechner und die Rechtschreibprüfung bieten die Option des lauten Vorlesens. Eine besondere Schwierigkeit stellen normalerweise gleich oder ähnlich klingende Wörter dar. Der Anwender kann jedoch über die Homophon-Kennzeichnung der Software die Wörter identifizieren und ändern, die er falsch verwendet hat. Die Scan- und Lesefunktionalitäten in Read&amp;Write GOLD stellen sicher, dass Bücher und Berichte genau in die Formate MS Word, HTML oder PDF übernommen werden.</p><h4 id="Herausforderung-1"><a href="#Herausforderung-1" class="headerlink" title="Herausforderung"></a>Herausforderung</h4><p>Um schwer auslesbaren Text aus dem Internet, wie zum Beispiel Inhalte aus Flash-Anwendungen, zu verarbeiten und laut vorlesen zu lassen, wird OCR-Technologie benötigt. Diese konvertiert Abbildungen von Text in „echten“ Text, der von der Texthelp Software verarbeitet und laut vorgelesen werden kann. Grafiken, Abbildungen oder Bilder führen normalerweise zu schlechteren Erkennungsergebnissen und stellen damit einen zusätzlichen Nachteil für Nutzer mit Legasthenie dar. Fast alle Lernmaterialien für Studenten, ob Bücher oder das Internet, enthalten graphische Elemente, was den Einsatz einer OCR-Software erfordert, die ohne großen Entwicklungsaufwand Bilder genauso gut erkennt wie Text.</p><h4 id="Herausforderungen-gemeinsam-meistern-wie-kann-ABBYY-Sie-unterstutzen"><a href="#Herausforderungen-gemeinsam-meistern-wie-kann-ABBYY-Sie-unterstutzen" class="headerlink" title="Herausforderungen gemeinsam meistern - wie kann ABBYY Sie unterstützen?"></a>Herausforderungen gemeinsam meistern - wie kann ABBYY Sie unterstützen?</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Losung-1"><a href="#Losung-1" class="headerlink" title="Lösung"></a>Lösung</h4><p>Texthelp implementierte ABBYY FineReader Engine, ein Software Development Kit (SDK), das die Entwicklung von Applikationen jeder Art und Größe ermöglicht und in fast jede Umgebung integriert werden kann. Texthelp war es wichtig, eine OCR-Lösung zu finden, die ohne wesentlichen Entwicklungsaufwand in die eigene Software implementiert werden konnte. Eine wichtige Anforderung war dabei die Fähigkeit, Texte aus Bildern auslesen zu können. Texthelp war es wichtig, die hier auftretenden Erkennungsprobleme zu lösen, und dank der Funktionen zur Umwandlung von PDFs und Field Level (Zonal) Erkennung erwies sich ABBYY FineReader Engine als die perfekte Lösung. Das SDK bietet eine hohe Erkennungsqualität von Bildzonen bzw. -ausschnitten, die relevante Daten enthalten. Diese Daten werden mittels hoch entwickelter Algorithmen konvertiert und dem Nutzer zur Verfügung gestellt. Die Genauigkeit in der Erkennung der Daten ist der Schlüssel zum bestmöglichen Ergebnis für die Anwender, also vollständig und korrekt wiedergegebene Informationen. ABBYY FineReader Engine basiert auf ABBYYs vielfach ausgezeichneter Technologie, die höchste Genauigkeit garantiert. „Früher mussten wir Text und Bild zur Unterscheidung in verschiedene Zonen einteilen, aber mit ABBYY FineReader Engine 8.1 ist das nicht mehr nötig, da die Zuordnung automatisch geschieht. Da Text in Abbildungen sehr wichtig sein kann, benötigten wir eine Software, die einfach zu bedienen ist und die Informationen dennoch sehr genau verarbeitet”, stellt Steve Menagh, Technical Development Manager bei Texthelp fest.</p><h4 id="Ergebnis-1"><a href="#Ergebnis-1" class="headerlink" title="Ergebnis"></a>Ergebnis</h4><p>Texthelp verbessert laufend seine preisgekrönte Read&amp;Write GOLD Software, um den Anwendern die bestmögliche Lesehilfe zu bieten. Mit der Implementierung von ABBYY FineReader Engine kann die positive Erfahrung der Anwender mit dem Programm zusätzlich gesteigert werden.</p><p> „Da Read&amp;Write GOLD auf allen öffentlichen PCs unserer Universität installiert ist, haben alle Studenten Zugriff darauf. Die Rückmeldungen der Studenten zeigen, dass die Möglichkeit, gedruckte Dokumente direkt in ein MS Word Dokument zu scannen und dieses sich dann mit Read&amp;Write vorlesen zu lassen, ganz besonders hilfreich ist.”</p><p> Andrew Dykes, Assistive Technology Service der Universität von Southampton.</p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14346/3-finereader-engine.jpg"                      alt="3-finereader-engine"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FineReader Engine <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Mehr erfahren <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14365/15-education.jpg"                      alt="15-education"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Bildung und Forschung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Mehr erfahren <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/8184/fallstudie-texthelp-bildungswesen-de.pdf" title="PDF-Version"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15361/cs-texthelp-360x162.jpg"                      alt="cs-texthelp-360x162"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/8184/fallstudie-texthelp-bildungswesen-de.pdf"  title="PDF-Version">PDF-Version <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/8184/fallstudie-texthelp-bildungswesen-de.pdf"  title="PDF-Version">Zum Dokument <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h6 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h6><p>Teilen  True ?  : “” </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Mehr über ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Alle ABBYY-Niederlassungen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713324&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVTV1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV TV Webcaster</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Sind-Sie-bereit-mit-einem-Experten-zu-sprechen"><a href="#Sind-Sie-bereit-mit-einem-Experten-zu-sprechen" class="headerlink" title="Sind Sie bereit, mit einem Experten zu sprechen?"></a>Sind Sie bereit, mit einem Experten zu sprechen?</h3><p>Wir würden Sie gerne auf Ihrem Weg zur Automatisierung unterstützen.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Texthelp-Und-ABBYY-Revolutionarer-Support-Fur-Menschen-Mit-Leseschwache-Oder-Dysgraphie&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Texthelp-Und-ABBYY-Revolutionarer</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Streamlined Workflow Integration with Pipefy &amp; ABBYY Document Automation</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/streamlined-workflow-integration-with-pipefy-and-abbyy-document-automation/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/streamlined-workflow-integration-with-pipefy-and-abbyy-document-automation/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.144Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.144Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Streamlined-Workflow-Integration-with-Pipefy-ABBYY-Document-Automation"><a href="#Streamlined-Workflow-Integration-with-Pipefy-ABBYY-Document-Automation" class="headerlink" title="Streamlined Workflow Integration with Pipefy &amp; ABBYY Document Automation"></a>Streamlined Workflow Integration with Pipefy &amp; ABBYY Document Automation</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Pipefy-and-ABBYY-establish-joint-solution-to-facilitate-document-based-process-automation"><a href="#Pipefy-and-ABBYY-establish-joint-solution-to-facilitate-document-based-process-automation" class="headerlink" title="Pipefy and ABBYY establish joint solution to facilitate document-based process automation"></a>Pipefy and ABBYY establish joint solution to facilitate document-based process automation</h2><p>May 18, 2023</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/33843/news-partners22.jpg"                      alt="News Partners22"                > </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.pipefy.com/" >Pipefy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, the low-code process automation platform, today announced a partnership with ABBYY, the industry leader in Intelligent Document Processing (IDP), to offer a powerful integrated solution that accelerates digital transformation initiatives ideal for use in people operations, financial services and insurance.</p><p>The integrated solution fuses Pipefy’s <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >process automation capabilities with ABBYY’s <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> optical character recognition (OCR) technology. Together, these two technologies take workflow and process optimization to a new level, by empowering non-technical users to build more efficient workflows while integrating cloud-based digital documents through data extracted by ABBYY’s artificial intelligence.</p><p>By deploying an IDP technology like ABBYY in tandem with Pipefy’s process automation platform, companies achieve dramatic gains in productivity and are able to make faster business decisions. The partnership offers increased speed and accuracy by turning process-related documents into data with a solution that reads, analyzes and processes the content like humans. This way, the joint solution improves processes with extensive document-driven manual work:</p><ul><li><strong>People Operations:</strong> According to a Gallup survey, 58% of organizations use onboarding resources for paper-intensive tasks. ABBYY provides pre-trained document skills that automate both the capturing and the analysis of HR onboarding documents. Pipefy automates all new hire communications and manual tasks to improve cross-team collaboration and data centralization, reducing new employee hiring time by 80%.</li><li><strong>Financial Service Operations:</strong> Finance teams get the perfect tools to automate document intake processes and streamline regulatory compliance. They can accelerate loan lifecycles by reducing complexity, enabling faster funding, and improving trade service quality levels (avoiding fraud and fines).</li><li><strong>Insurance:</strong> The integration between ABBYY and Pipefy means faster, more accurate underwriting, quoting, customer onboarding, and endorsement processing. It enables increased new business and renewal retention. On the claims side, it can also ease the First Notice of Loss, repair estimate reviews, and settlement invoices processing.</li></ul><p>“ABBYY simplifies how companies process their documents in a low-code&#x2F;no-code environment.<br>As a result, companies can automate manual processes, work in modern architecture, and achieve faster time to implementation – all resulting in better outcomes for customers and the business.”</p><p><em>Bruce Orcutt, SVP of Product Marketing at ABBYY</em></p><p>“Pipefy and ABBYY combine low-code process automation with efficient document processing.”</p><p><em>Wanessa Siewert, Pipefy’s Program and Alliances Manager</em></p><p>“The joint solution is critical to accelerate digital transformation in departments where a paperwork-prone culture would place obstacles to process excellence and efficiency.”</p><p><em>Gustavo de Martini, Pipefy’s Vice President of Partners</em></p><h3 id="About-ABBYY"><a href="#About-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="About ABBYY"></a>About ABBYY</h3><p>ABBYY powers intelligent automation. We reimagine the way people work and the way companies accelerate business by delivering the intelligence that fuels automation platforms. Our solutions transform enterprise data and empower you with the insights you need to work smarter and faster. We help more than 10,000 companies globally, including many of the Fortune 500, to drive significant impact where it matters most: customer experience, profitability, and competitive advantage. More information visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/company/about-us/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and follow us on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/abbyy" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://twitter.com/ABBYY%5FSoftware" >Twitter <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://www.facebook.com/ABBYYsoft" >Facebook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>ABBYY can either be a registered trademark or a trademark and can also be a logo, a company name (or part of it), or part of a product name of ABBYY group companies and may not be used without consent of its respective owners.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ephamedtechinc.pxf.io/c/5597632/2097466/26400?prodsku=B700" target="_top" id="2097466"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/26400-2097466"                      border="0" alt="" width="2048" height="1024"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2097466/26400"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="About-Pipefy"><a href="#About-Pipefy" class="headerlink" title="About Pipefy"></a>About Pipefy</h3><p>Pipefy is the low-code process automation platform that increases team productivity and efficiency, centralizes data, and standardizes processes for teams in IT, Finance, HR, Customer Operations, and more. Through its workflow automation and low-code framework, Pipefy helps businesses achieve stack extensibility and process excellence for every team in every department, delivering 3-digit ROI to its customers. Among its many recognitions, Pipefy was named to the <a class="link"   href="https://www.globenewswire.com/Tracker?data=L4P4CtPwtdXtpVLiV6cfqyiiRtxpBqyS2SAXp-Uu3aDCUyG3QAi5wQaOrJhTvsG9CfLh3GwDtY7OUnu6pkJh4akYx_cDwV9_PwVdssnM23XANkv74ij3fskp4E8dyyEzcEDgIMPPH1qiFcz-No4K6xVUIjdxlE1kGZJFCO7raCaNZJOFKtl32Fn9gUKPcciiT5vwVF5cuxUd4QIlmM1Klbyq3ZpqnXouCvINiDiNywZMKPOygKPBVa0fp1BTtTdIFJbcz7rdKtI-Lczo53lOfJrB7RsuEEvNTEDQ1vStbicQLWAeeJr3urPr_VRFgKpLVikSHwAC3Twf95EkpnYx0u5qlIo0VxCuGW6NMe-uMl-ZLsGk6sEUTDDmkrSU2P46" >Deloitte Technology Fast 500™ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, a ranking of the 500 fastest-growing companies in North America in November, 2022.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713324&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVTV1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV TV Webcaster</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="ABBYY-Editorial-Contact"><a href="#ABBYY-Editorial-Contact" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Editorial Contact"></a>ABBYY Editorial Contact</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/23662/02d-ginaray.png"                      alt="02D Ginaray"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://homestyler.sjv.io/c/5597632/2044747/22993" target="_top" id="2044747"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/22993-2044747"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2044747/22993"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Gina-Ray"><a href="#Gina-Ray" class="headerlink" title="Gina Ray"></a>Gina Ray</h4><p><em>ABBYY</em></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >gina.ray@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Streamlined-Workflow-Integration-with-Pipefy-ABBYY-Document-Automation&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Streamlined-Workflow-Integration-with-Pipefy-ABBYY</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Integration of AI and Robotics in Modern Medicine - Infographic Guide</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/smart-integration-of-ai-and-robotics-in-modern-medicine-infographic-guide/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/smart-integration-of-ai-and-robotics-in-modern-medicine-infographic-guide/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.136Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.136Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Smart-Integration-of-AI-and-Robotics-in-Modern-Medicine-Infographic-Guide"><a href="#Smart-Integration-of-AI-and-Robotics-in-Modern-Medicine-Infographic-Guide" class="headerlink" title="Smart Integration of AI and Robotics in Modern Medicine - Infographic Guide"></a>Smart Integration of AI and Robotics in Modern Medicine - Infographic Guide</h2><p>1&#x2F; 1100%实际尺寸适合宽度适合高度适合页面自动</p><p>91% of healthcare leaders reported an ROI equal to or greater than their initial investment 52% reported up to 3x ROI 49% also reported improved efficiency and productivity among employees 67% of HCOs reported increased happiness among employees since implementing intelligent automation 60% said their employees engaged in higher value &#x2F; more interesting work 57% reported increased staff retention 48% of providers plan to increase intelligent automation in their organization 29% plan to invest in low-code&#x2F; no-code solutions 44% are prioritizing customer onboarding 37% are prioritizing AP automation 37% are prioritizing customer experience of healthcare organizations (HCOs) reported increased automation budgets reported investing $300,000 or more in 2023 84% 43% What benefits did intelligent automation bring to providers, employees, and patients over the last 12 months, and how do healthcare organizations plan to invest in 2024? © ABBYY 2024. ABBYY is a registered trademark or a trademark of ABBYY Development Inc. and&#x2F;or its affiliates. This designation can also be logo, product, or company name (or part of any of the above) of ABBYY Development Inc. and&#x2F;or its affiliates and may not be used without consent of their respective owners. All other product names and trademarks mentioned herein are the property of their respective owners. DS-428 Driving business value for healthcare providers Accelerating and improving patient outcomes Enhancing employee experience and efficiency Providers’ plans for investment in the next 12 months Read more about ABBYY’s purpose-built AI solutions for healthcare automation <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >here <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> . 52% of HCOs reported faster delivery of value and service 43% reported higher quality service 32% reported reduced prices for services Intelligent Automation in Healthcare 2023: Benefits, Trends &amp; Priorities Our recent survey of healthcare organizations confirms that the healthcare sector is expanding its investment in artificial intelligence for intelligent automation. </p><p>0&#x2F;0</p><p>匹配案例每页限制结果 1 个</p><p>1&#x2F; 1100%实际尺寸适合宽度适合高度适合页面自动</p><p>91% of healthcare leaders reported an ROI equal to or greater than their initial investment 52% reported up to 3x ROI 49% also reported improved efficiency and productivity among employees 67% of HCOs reported increased happiness among employees since implementing intelligent automation 60% said their employees engaged in higher value &#x2F; more interesting work 57% reported increased staff retention 48% of providers plan to increase intelligent automation in their organization 29% plan to invest in low-code&#x2F; no-code solutions 44% are prioritizing customer onboarding 37% are prioritizing AP automation 37% are prioritizing customer experience of healthcare organizations (HCOs) reported increased automation budgets reported investing $300,000 or more in 2023 84% 43% What benefits did intelligent automation bring to providers, employees, and patients over the last 12 months, and how do healthcare organizations plan to invest in 2024? © ABBYY 2024. ABBYY is a registered trademark or a trademark of ABBYY Development Inc. and&#x2F;or its affiliates. This designation can also be logo, product, or company name (or part of any of the above) of ABBYY Development Inc. and&#x2F;or its affiliates and may not be used without consent of their respective owners. All other product names and trademarks mentioned herein are the property of their respective owners. DS-428 Driving business value for healthcare providers Accelerating and improving patient outcomes Enhancing employee experience and efficiency Providers’ plans for investment in the next 12 months Read more about ABBYY’s purpose-built AI solutions for healthcare automation <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >here <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> . 52% of HCOs reported faster delivery of value and service 43% reported higher quality service 32% reported reduced prices for services Intelligent Automation in Healthcare 2023: Benefits, Trends &amp; Priorities Our recent survey of healthcare organizations confirms that the healthcare sector is expanding its investment in artificial intelligence for intelligent automation. </p><p><a href="https://www.idrsolutions.com/online-pdf-to-html-converter"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.abbyy.com/buildvu-logo.png"                      alt="Created with BuildVu"                ></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://zonlipartnershipprogram.pxf.io/c/5597632/1611407/17882" target="_top" id="1611407"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17882-1611407"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="485"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1611407/17882"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Smart-Integration-of-AI-and-Robotics-in-Modern-Medicine-Infographic-Guide&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Smart-Integration-of-AI-and-Robotics-in-Modern-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revolutionize Your IT Infrastructure Using AI: Essential Strategies by ABBYY Experts</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/revolutionize-your-it-infrastructure-using-ai-essential-strategies-by-abbyy-experts/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/revolutionize-your-it-infrastructure-using-ai-essential-strategies-by-abbyy-experts/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.130Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.130Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revolutionize-Your-IT-Infrastructure-Using-AI-Essential-Strategies-by-ABBYY-Experts"><a href="#Revolutionize-Your-IT-Infrastructure-Using-AI-Essential-Strategies-by-ABBYY-Experts" class="headerlink" title="Revolutionize Your IT Infrastructure Using AI: Essential Strategies by ABBYY Experts"></a>Revolutionize Your IT Infrastructure Using AI: Essential Strategies by ABBYY Experts</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to The Intelligent Enterprise <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Putting-the-“AI”-in-Team"><a href="#Putting-the-“AI”-in-Team" class="headerlink" title="Putting the “AI” in Team:"></a>Putting the “AI” in Team:</h2><p>How a Winning Tech Stack<br>Changes the Game</p><h6 id="by-Max-Vermeir-Senior-Director-of-AI-Strategy"><a href="#by-Max-Vermeir-Senior-Director-of-AI-Strategy" class="headerlink" title="by Max Vermeir, Senior Director of AI Strategy"></a>by Max Vermeir, Senior Director of AI Strategy</h6><p>An effective automation fabric is built upon high-quality data, guided by a strategically designed roadmap, and supported by a strong integration team. We’ve seen our customers experience the most success when they practice the following three principles: process understanding; technology assessment; strategic implementation.</p><p>As the artificial intelligence (AI) hype cycle continues to run its course, a collective consciousness of <a class="link"   href="https://www.cdotrends.com/story/3915/hype-machine-workhorse-practical-ai-new-black" >practicality and strategy in AI use <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> has begun to play a larger role in how these solutions are utilized by enterprises globally.</p><p>Perceptions of AI-powered solutions have progressed from an initial “one-size-fits-all” mindset to a more goal-oriented and intentional approach, veering in the direction of solving specific business challenges and generating value in high-priority areas with a more acute understanding of AI’s strengths and weaknesses.</p><p>So, what’s the next step for maturity in businesses’ use of AI? </p><p>According to Forrester, it’s <a class="link"   href="https://www.forrester.com/report/take-the-first-steps-toward-an-automation-fabric/RES177540" >weaving an automation fabric <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> that is capable of supporting complex end-to-end processes across the organization; an automation fabric that is comprised of key players, each excelling in their roles to tackle objectives that might have otherwise been impossible. </p><p>We see our customers currently navigating this approach, inspired to implement more AI-based solutions into their processes while ensuring that these solutions are both purpose-built for their business needs and positioned to augment their existing tech stack.</p><p>One customer, a leading global sportswear manufacturer, is putting the “AI” in team particularly well. They recently made game-changing strides toward expanding and strengthening their automation fabric, implementing AI-powered intelligent document processing (IDP) to integrate with their existing robotic process automation (RPA) solution and defining a strategy to incorporate a variety of AI-enabled technologies into a winning team.</p><h3 id="Using-IDP-to-make-RPA-more-effective"><a href="#Using-IDP-to-make-RPA-more-effective" class="headerlink" title="Using IDP to make RPA more effective"></a>Using IDP to make RPA more effective</h3><p>After selling one of its large subsidiary brands, the sportswear company was faced with a massive document challenge: segregating and sorting 27 million documents associated with the two entities. Two and a half million of these documents lacked any standardized format, structure, or obvious indication of which document belonged to what company. </p><p>Wanting to take an AI-driven approach to solving this challenge, they decided to integrate ABBYY’s AI-powered OCR with their existing RPA system. The combined solution scanned the documents for specified trigger words, company codes, and other differentiating factors to sort them into the appropriate folder for each brand. As a result, the global company was able to successfully sell the subsidiary brand without any penalty or complications resulting from missing or errantly processed documents. </p><p>Without this strategic synergy of solutions, the manual processing and sorting of millions of documents would have consumed an unsustainable amount of time and resources, while increasing susceptibility to errors. </p><p>This use case isn’t just a proof point for the value of <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY OCR <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> in processing large volumes of unstructured documents, but also a testament to the strength and efficacy of the global company’s automation fabric. </p><p>Checklist</p><h4 id="Action-Steps-for-Building-an-AI-Ready-Organization"><a href="#Action-Steps-for-Building-an-AI-Ready-Organization" class="headerlink" title="Action Steps for Building an AI-Ready Organization"></a>Action Steps for Building an AI-Ready Organization</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/-/jssmedia/project/abbyy/abbyy/insights/resource-center/pdfs/checklist-intelligent-automation-is-your-organization-ai-ready-en.pdf" >Download <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ukaidot.sjv.io/c/5597632/1793237/19578" target="_top" id="1793237"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/19578-1793237"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="1200"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1793237/19578"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Identifying-a-game-changing-tech-stack"><a href="#Identifying-a-game-changing-tech-stack" class="headerlink" title="Identifying a game-changing tech stack"></a>Identifying a game-changing tech stack</h3><p>The athleticwear giant is no stranger to assembling a winning team of solutions. They’ve carefully designed a “digital playbook” to AI-enable digital platforms for the full end-to-end process lifecycle, dividing their approach into five stages: discovery, analysis, improvement, standardization, and finally automation. </p><p>Each stage incorporates a combination of AI-enabled technologies and platforms: </p><ul><li>Business process management and mining (BPMM)</li><li>Intelligent document processing and archiving (IDPA – ABBYY is here)</li><li>Low-code &#x2F; no-code</li><li>Workflow automation (WFA)</li><li>Robotic process automation (RPA)</li><li>Backend automation (BEA)</li></ul><p>This digital playbook has supported multiple digitization initiatives for the organization and will continue to do so in the future as they look towards additional application integrations with automation tools. For example, they’ve also automated invoice processing in their <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >accounts payable <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> workflow using ABBYY IDP, yielding a 53% straight-through processing rate. </p><p>Innovation leaders striving for the same value and adaptability, take note: with the right approach, your organization can also build a game-changing tech stack.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://estore.zonealarm.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=36245101&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://sc1.checkpoint.com/sc1/za/images/boxes/zang_box_trust.png"                      border="0"                >ZoneAlarm Extreme Security NextGen</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Building-an-AI-ready-organization"><a href="#Building-an-AI-ready-organization" class="headerlink" title="Building an AI-ready organization"></a>Building an AI-ready organization</h3><p>An effective automation fabric is built upon high-quality data, guided by a strategically designed roadmap, and supported by a strong integration team. We’ve seen our customers experience the most success when they practice the following three principles: </p><ul><li><strong>Process understanding</strong>. Having a thorough and data-driven understanding of your organization’s processes is crucial for identifying the best opportunities for automation. Auditing your data landscape for potential discrepancies in quality and structure will ensure that your automation initiatives are effective, and your AI platforms are working with reliably accurate data.</li><li><strong>Technology assessment</strong>. By assessing your current technology stack and outlining milestones, objectives, and desired outcomes, you can then develop a phased implementation plan that includes deployment, integration with existing systems, and scalability considerations. Defining KPIs and metrics to measure the impacts on operational efficiency and customer satisfaction will enable you to ensure you’ve incorporated the right solutions in the right areas of your business.</li><li><strong>Strategic implementation</strong>. The last step is strategically selecting the right AI tools for your business and the right partners to implement them. ABBYY’s 35 years of experience in AI and IDP technologies enable strong support from planning to full-scale implementation, with dedicated collaboration that provides access to both innovative technologies and expansive knowledge of best practices.</li></ul><p>Even with AI, some business challenges are too complex to be solved by any single technology, tool, platform, or solution. But with in-depth knowledge of your business data and the support of a dependable partner like ABBYY, your business can establish a suite of automation solutions effective enough to wholly transform your operations. </p><p>Ready to harness the power of AI in your organization? Download our free checklist, <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/-/jssmedia/project/abbyy/abbyy/insights/resource-center/pdfs/checklist-intelligent-automation-is-your-organization-ai-ready-en.pdf" >Action Steps for Building an AI-Ready Organization with ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for updates"></a>Subscribe for updates</h4><p>Get updated on the latest insights and perspectives for business &amp; technology leaders</p><p>First name*</p><p>Last name</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revolutionize-Your-IT-Infrastructure-Using-AI-Essential-Strategies-by-ABBYY-Experts&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revolutionize-Your-IT-Infrastructure-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Personalized Marketing with Cookiebot Technology Integration</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/personalized-marketing-with-cookiebot-technology-integration/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/personalized-marketing-with-cookiebot-technology-integration/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.119Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.119Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Personalized-Marketing-with-Cookiebot-Technology-Integration"><a href="#Personalized-Marketing-with-Cookiebot-Technology-Integration" class="headerlink" title="Personalized Marketing with Cookiebot Technology Integration"></a>Personalized Marketing with Cookiebot Technology Integration</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-FineReader-15-Makes-the-First-Step-to-Digital-Transformation-Faster-and-Easier"><a href="#ABBYY-FineReader-15-Makes-the-First-Step-to-Digital-Transformation-Faster-and-Easier" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY FineReader 15 Makes the First Step to Digital Transformation Faster and Easier"></a>ABBYY FineReader 15 Makes the First Step to Digital Transformation Faster and Easier</h2><p>August 27, 2019</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><h4 id="The-comprehensive-PDF-tool-significantly-improves-document-productivity-in-the-digital-workplace"><a href="#The-comprehensive-PDF-tool-significantly-improves-document-productivity-in-the-digital-workplace" class="headerlink" title="The comprehensive PDF tool significantly improves document productivity in the digital workplace."></a><em>The comprehensive PDF tool significantly improves document productivity in the digital workplace.</em></h4><p>ABBYY, a global leader in Digital IQ technologies and solutions, today announced the release of ABBYY FineReader 15, an enhanced PDF application for Windows that empowers users to manage any kind of document in the digital workplace. With billions of scanned and digitally born PDF documents opened every year, information workers in SMBs and enterprises require a productivity tool that makes working with any type of PDF simple and efficient. Powered by ABBYY’s AI-based text recognition technology, the new FineReader 15 has received paragraph-level editing and layout adjustment in both digital and scanned PDFs, significant improvements in text recognition and documents comparison quality, faster viewing, and easy deployment with modern virtualization solutions.</p><p>“Digitizing documents is the first step in a company’s digital transformation journey, and PDF has become the standard format. However, even if paper documents are digitized, they are often not accessible or searchable,” comments <strong>Slavena Hristova</strong>, Director of Product Marketing at ABBYY. “FineReader gives workers the tools they need to truly incorporate both digital and paper documents into a unified workflow and overcome the pain points of working with PDF files.”</p><p>Thanks to the newly received paragraph-level editing and layout adjustment, FineReader 15 makes editing PDFs almost as easy as DOCX documents: text flows smoothly from line to line, while paragraphs and pictures can be rearranged to adjust the overall layout. The new way of exporting document comparison results as a Microsoft® Word document with differences shown in the “track changes” mode make collaboration easier, document workflows smoother and faster.</p><p>FineReader 15 boasts even more precise analysis and conversion of tables, better automatic tagging for PDF and PDF&#x2F;UA creation, and better detection of headers and footers. The application also offers intelligent detection of text-layer quality for digitally created PDFs allowing for more accurate results when converting digital PDFs into editable formats or comparing documents. Additionally, it delivers up to 55% faster PDF document viewing and opening as well as even higher OCR accuracy: up to 98% overall accuracy for Korean and Chinese, up to 97% for Japanese.</p><p>ABBYY FineReader 15 offers accessible tools to collaborate, edit, and reuse digital and paper documents efficiently, thus improving communication and performance in a digital workplace. To promote a digital working environment, the PDF application also addresses pain points from paper-based workflows such as highlighting, commenting, signing, stamping, redacting, comparing versions, collecting feedback and more.</p><p>FineReader 15 is available worldwide via the ABBYY online store and a wide network of reselling partners. The Standard and Corporate versions are available for individual use as well as in volume licensing options for organizations. Visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/finereader <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for additional information on features, prices, or to download a trial.</p><p>ABBYY offers solutions for every step of an organization’s digital transformation journey with intelligent technologies that help businesses and information workers achieve greater efficiency, accelerate decision-making, and drive revenue. Ranging from scanning and document recognition to data capture, text analytics, AI and process intelligence, ABBYY solutions integrate across the entire information lifecycle.</p><p><strong>About ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY is a global leader in Digital IQ technologies and solutions. ABBYY offers a complete range of AI-based technologies and solutions getting insight from business content and processes. By providing digital transformation solutions to financial services, insurance, transportation, healthcare, and other industries, the company helps organizations achieve the next wave of growth by understanding customers and delivering responsive real-time intelligent systems. The flexibility of ABBYY AI solutions enables customers to utilize a diverse range of advanced technologies, platforms and solutions for process analytics and intelligence, classification, text analytics, data and entity extraction, and data validation via any communication channel and in any format. ABBYY technologies are used and licensed by some of the largest international enterprises and government organizations, as well as SMBs and individuals. The company maintains offices in Australia, Cyprus, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, Spain, Taiwan, the UK, Ukraine, and the United States. For more information, please visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/company <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY and the ABBYY Logo are either registered trademarks or trademarks of ABBYY Software Ltd. Other product names mentioned herein may be trademarks and&#x2F;or registered trademarks of their respective owners and are hereby recognized.</em></p><p><strong>Editorial Contact:</strong></p><p>Gina Ray, APR</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >gina@raypr.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>+1-949-370-0941</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://caperobbin.sjv.io/c/5597632/2006118/18460" target="_top" id="2006118"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18460-2006118"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2006118/18460"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Personalized-Marketing-with-Cookiebot-Technology-Integration&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Personalized-Marketing-with-Cookiebot-Technology-Integration</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Participate in the Exclusive ABBYY Smart Automation Event of May 2024</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/participate-in-the-exclusive-abbyy-smart-automation-event-of-may-2024/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/participate-in-the-exclusive-abbyy-smart-automation-event-of-may-2024/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.112Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.112Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Participate-in-the-Exclusive-ABBYY-Smart-Automation-Event-of-May-2024"><a href="#Participate-in-the-Exclusive-ABBYY-Smart-Automation-Event-of-May-2024" class="headerlink" title="Participate in the Exclusive ABBYY Smart Automation Event of May 2024"></a>Participate in the Exclusive ABBYY Smart Automation Event of May 2024</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-2nd-Annual-Intelligent-Automation-Month-Highlights-the-Power-of-Purpose-Built-AI-to-Accelerate-Business"><a href="#ABBYY-2nd-Annual-Intelligent-Automation-Month-Highlights-the-Power-of-Purpose-Built-AI-to-Accelerate-Business" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY 2nd Annual Intelligent Automation Month Highlights the Power of Purpose-Built AI to Accelerate Business"></a>ABBYY 2nd Annual Intelligent Automation Month Highlights the Power of Purpose-Built AI to Accelerate Business</h2><p>August 14, 2024</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><h5 id="During-September-global-innovation-experts-educate-business-and-IT-leaders-how-to-increase-efficiencies-and-ROI-using-AI"><a href="#During-September-global-innovation-experts-educate-business-and-IT-leaders-how-to-increase-efficiencies-and-ROI-using-AI" class="headerlink" title="During September, global innovation experts educate business and IT leaders how to increase efficiencies and ROI using AI"></a>During September, global innovation experts educate business and IT leaders how to increase efficiencies and ROI using AI</h5><p>The second annual <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Intelligent Automation Month <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> takes place during September 2024 with online programs designed to help organizations from every industry understand the impact of purpose-built AI and how it can advance their business.</p><p>Weekly webinars will provide accessible and digestible information based on real-world applications, best practices, and current research that will help attendees know how to identify automation opportunities, navigate AI compliance and prepare for new regulations. Attendees will learn the benefits of key AI-powered intelligent automation technologies including process intelligence and intelligent document processing (IDP), including valuable input from customers, partners and technology influencers on how to strategically leverage AI and automation to maximize ROI.</p><p>Business and IT leaders and journalists are invited to join ABBYY in the following sessions to gain first-hand knowledge about overcoming common business challenges and achieving success with AI. These sessions will include industry experts alongside ABBYY leaders.</p><ul><li><strong>September 5th: The inevitable wave of AI regulations; balancing utility and harms</strong>. This crucial session will break down the latest global AI regulations and compliance best practices. ForHumanity, a public non-profit organization focusing on independent auditing of AI systems, will provide important information to attendees on ensuring safe and trustworthy AI methods, along with cybersecurity considerations from ABBYY.</li><li><strong>September 12th: E-invoicing is coming! Is your organization ready?</strong> You will be ready after this webinar. Featuring Billentis, we’ll enlighten you on the current state of e-invoicing globally, with specific focus on Europe. We’ll discuss trend projections, the e-invoicing process, solutions involved (e-invoicing platforms, PEPPOL, etc.), and how purpose-built IDP aligns with business needs for efficient invoice processing.</li><li><strong>September 19th: Panel with innovation leaders.</strong> This fireside chat with executives from global financial institution, ING, and the Reveal Group, a global intelligent automation services company, will enlighten you on the latest AI tech trends and show the real-world ROI of using purpose-built AI to solve common business challenges.</li><li><strong>September 26th: Take the guess work out of your intelligent automation deployment with process intelligence</strong>. Doculabs and ABBYY will discuss how to use process mining and task mining to give you data-driven insights to ensure you are leveraging AI to maximize operational efficiency.</li></ul><p>Intelligent Automation Month is an important industry initiative that puts a spotlight on what businesses can achieve with purpose-built AI.</p><p>Attendees will feel encouraged by the panel of experts featured during September and have actionable insights for how to plan, deploy and measure the ROI of their AI investments for their organizations.</p><p>Bruce Orcutt, CMO at ABBYY</p><p>Take your organization to the next level of operational efficiency by registering for Intelligent Automation Month sessions today at <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/intelligent-automation-month/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><h3 id="About-ABBYY"><a href="#About-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="About ABBYY"></a>About ABBYY</h3><p>ABBYY puts your information to work with purpose-built AI. We combine innovation and experience to transform data from business-critical documents into intelligent actionable outcomes in over 200 languages in real time. We are trusted by more than 10,000 companies globally, including many of the Fortune 500, to drive significant impact where it matters most: accelerate the customer experience, operational excellence, and competitive advantage. ABBYY is a global company with headquarters in Milpitas, CA and offices in 13 countries, and is the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Official Intelligent Automation Partner of Arsenal Women Football Club <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. For more information, visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/company <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and follow us on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/abbyy" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://twitter.com/ABBYY%5FSoftware" >Twitter <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://www.facebook.com/ABBYYsoft" >Facebook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, and <a class="link"   href="https://www.instagram.com/abbyyglobal/" >Instagram <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>ABBYY can either be a registered trademark or a trademark and can also be a logo, a company name (or part of it), or part of a product name of ABBYY group companies and may not be used without consent of its respective owners.</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.revouninstaller.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=28010250&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/4282ec8de8c9be897e7aff4aa231b1a4/336__280a.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Participate-in-the-Exclusive-ABBYY-Smart-Automation-Event-of-May-2024&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Participate-in-the-Exclusive-ABBYY-Smart-Automation</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Optimizing Business Processes: How ABBYY Complements Automation Anywhere Solutions</title>
    <link href="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/optimizing-business-processes-how-abbyy-complements-automation-anywhere-solutions/"/>
    <id>https://solve-info.techidaily.com/optimizing-business-processes-how-abbyy-complements-automation-anywhere-solutions/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:06:08.106Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:06:08.106Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Optimizing-Business-Processes-How-ABBYY-Complements-Automation-Anywhere-Solutions"><a href="#Optimizing-Business-Processes-How-ABBYY-Complements-Automation-Anywhere-Solutions" class="headerlink" title="Optimizing Business Processes: How ABBYY Complements Automation Anywhere Solutions"></a>Optimizing Business Processes: How ABBYY Complements Automation Anywhere Solutions</h2><h2 id=""><a href="#" class="headerlink" title=""></a></h2><h2 id="ABBYY-Automation-Anywhere"><a href="#ABBYY-Automation-Anywhere" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY | Automation Anywhere"></a>ABBYY | Automation Anywhere</h2><p>Kombinieren Sie Bots von Automation Anywhere mit intelligenter Dokumentenverarbeitung, um Inhalte zu verstehen und aus einer Vielzahl von strukturierten wie unstrukturierten Dokumentarten Informationen zu extrahieren.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h4 id="Die-Kombination-aus-ABBYY-Automation-Anywhere-Technologien"><a href="#Die-Kombination-aus-ABBYY-Automation-Anywhere-Technologien" class="headerlink" title="Die Kombination aus ABBYY + Automation Anywhere Technologien"></a>Die Kombination aus ABBYY + Automation Anywhere Technologien</h4><p>RPA-Lösungen von Automation Anywhere ermöglichen es Unternehmen in den unterschiedlichsten Branchen, kritische Geschäftsprozesse zu automatisieren. ABBYY-Lösungen bieten diesen Unternehmen zudem die Möglichkeit, auf wertvolle Informationen aus einer Vielzahl von strukturierten wie unstrukturierten Geschäftsdokumenten zuzugreifen und ihre Automatisierungsinitiativen so zu optimieren.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/solutions/digital-onboarding/overview-image.jpg?h=716&iar=0&w=1272"                                     ></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/solutions/digital-document-archiving/drawer-image.jpg?h=392&iar=0&w=696"                                     ></p><h4 id="Wie-ABBYY-und-Automation-Anywhere-zusammenwirken"><a href="#Wie-ABBYY-und-Automation-Anywhere-zusammenwirken" class="headerlink" title="Wie ABBYY und Automation Anywhere zusammenwirken"></a>Wie ABBYY und Automation Anywhere zusammenwirken</h4><p>ABBYYs Lösung für Automation Anywhere bietet Ihnen folgende Möglichkeiten: </p><ul><li>Binden Sie die führenden intelligenten Datenverarbeitungslösungen von ABBYY direkt in Automation Anywhere Enterprise RPA ein, um in Ihrer Prozessautomatisierung über einfache Szenarien hinauszugehen.</li><li>Setzen Sie auf OCR-, Dokumentenklassifizierungs- und Datenextraktionsfunktionen der neuesten Generation, die strukturierte und unstrukturierte, einfache oder komplexe Geschäftsdokumente verstehen und verarbeiten können.</li><li>Automatisieren Sie die Klassifizierung von Dokumenten und die Extraktion von Daten durch kontinuierliches Auto-Learning und Benutzereingaben.</li><li>Erzielen Sie durch die Automatisierung inhaltsbasierter Prozesse auf der Grundlage von Dokumenten, Bildern und Scans mit RPA die gewünschten Ergebnisse und einen optimalen Unternehmenserfolg.</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.systoolsgroup.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=SYSTOOBY&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.systoolsgroup.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DSysTools%2BSQL%2BRecovery"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.systoolsgroup.com/box/sql-recovery.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Vorteile-der-Integration"><a href="#Vorteile-der-Integration" class="headerlink" title="Vorteile der Integration"></a>Vorteile der Integration</h2><h5 id="Automatisieren-Sie-verschiedenste-dokumentenbasier­te-Geschaftsentschei­dungen"><a href="#Automatisieren-Sie-verschiedenste-dokumentenbasier­te-Geschaftsentschei­dungen" class="headerlink" title="Automatisieren Sie verschiedenste dokumentenbasier­te Geschäftsentschei­dungen"></a>Automatisieren Sie verschiedenste dokumentenbasier­te Geschäftsentschei­dungen</h5><p>Nutzen Sie in Ihren Robotikprozessen implementierte KI- und Machine Learning-Funktionen der neuesten Generation, um komplexe Dokumente und Prozesse ganz einfach zu bearbeiten.</p><h5 id="Steigern-Sie-die-Prozess-Compliance"><a href="#Steigern-Sie-die-Prozess-Compliance" class="headerlink" title="Steigern Sie die Prozess-Compliance"></a>Steigern Sie die Prozess-Compliance</h5><p>Lassen Sie Roboter geschäftskritische Dokumente in strukturierte Daten umwandeln und gemäß dem gewünschten Prozesspfad angemessene Entscheidungen treffen, sodass menschliche Mitarbeiter nur in Ausnahmesituationen eingreifen müssen.</p><h5 id="Gehen-Sie-uber-einfache-RPA-Szenarien-hinaus"><a href="#Gehen-Sie-uber-einfache-RPA-Szenarien-hinaus" class="headerlink" title="Gehen Sie über einfache RPA-Szenarien hinaus"></a>Gehen Sie über einfache RPA-Szenarien hinaus</h5><p>Erzielen Sie mit Initiativen zur Prozessautomatisierung einen höheren Mehrwert und Geschäftserfolg, indem Sie komplexe Kernprozesse nutzen, die von Ihren digitalen Mitarbeitern für eine effiziente Unterstützung Ihrer menschlichen Mitarbeiter intelligente Funktionen verlangen.</p><h5 id="Erweitern-Sie-Roboter-um-Fahigkeiten-zum-Verstehen-von-Inhalten"><a href="#Erweitern-Sie-Roboter-um-Fahigkeiten-zum-Verstehen-von-Inhalten" class="headerlink" title="Erweitern Sie Roboter um Fähigkeiten zum Verstehen von Inhalten"></a>Erweitern Sie Roboter um Fähigkeiten zum Verstehen von Inhalten</h5><p>Steigern Sie den Mehrwert Ihrer Prozessautomatisierung, indem Sie Ihre digitalen Mitarbeiter in die Lage versetzen, Geschäftsdokumente jeder Art zu verstehen und darin enthaltene Daten zu extrahieren, um auf dieser Grundlage intelligente Entscheidungen zu treffen. </p><p>ABBYY FlexiCapture-Konnektor für Automation Anywhere (BETA) </p><p>Der ABBYY FlexiCapture-Konnektor für Automation Anywhere ist ein Meta-Bot, der die Integration der Enterprise-Plattform FlexiCapture in Automation Anywhere Enterprise RPA und damit die automatisierte Verarbeitung unstrukturierter Inhalte wie Dokumente, Bilder und Text und deren Umwandlung in strukturierte, bearbeitbare Daten ermöglicht.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Konnektor herunterladen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/feature/basecomponents/clients/automationanywhere_logo_rev_120px.png?h=44&iar=0&w=120"                                     ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4576829&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/9e740b84bb48a64dde25061566299467/products/copy_1_jp_box_big.png"                      border="0"                >Jet Profiler for MySQL, Enterprise Version： Jet Profiler for MySQL is real-time query performance and diagnostics tool for the MySQL database server. Its detailed query information, graphical interface and ease of use makes this a great tool for finding performance bottlenecks in your MySQL databases. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.systoolsgroup.com/affiliate.php?ACCOUNT=SYSTOOBY&AFFILIATE=108875&PATH=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.systoolsgroup.com%3FAFFILIATE%3D108875%26RESOURCE%3DSysTools%2BGmail%2BBackup"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.systoolsgroup.com/box/gmail-backup.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Mochten-Sie-mit-unserem-Expertenteam-sprechen"><a href="#Mochten-Sie-mit-unserem-Expertenteam-sprechen" class="headerlink" title="Möchten Sie mit unserem Expertenteam sprechen?"></a>Möchten Sie mit unserem Expertenteam sprechen?</h3><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Demo vereinbaren <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontakt aufnehmen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Optimizing-Business-Processes-How-ABBYY-Complements-Automation-Anywhere-Solutions&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Optimizing-Business-Processes-How-ABBYY</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-info.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
